HDZIMU http://www.hdzimu.com
HDZIMU中文字幕W http://www.hdzimu.com
[Internet Enthusiasts]
Wj酆谜叻g
You bought this? Yeah.
你I了@啊 是啊
And it's ours now. We own this. Mm-hmm.
F在是我的了 ~哼
I love it. Right?
我凵线@里了 是的吧
What'd I tell you? The fireplace, the built-ins here.
我就跟你f嘛 你看@惹妒降谋t
Are you sure you want to give this to your sister?
你_定就o你姐妹@
Babe, we'd make 100K off this flip all day long.
我花了一整天跑了百公里^戆
Trying to make up... This is it?
花心思整理一下h 就@
Hey, yeah. Come in. You guys made me ask off an hour early to see
啊 是的 M戆 你z叫我早硪^就榱
this dump?
@垃圾
We're all smelling this, right? Yeah, it smells like I'm
我都深有感受不是么 是啊 感X就像
breathing piss.
我在呼吸新r的排泄物
Okay. Not a good fit. So we'll just go.
]e 不是好地方 我so走
Come on. Come on. Have a little vision.
走吧 拜托 再看看嘛
French doors to the garden.
看看@法式木T 通向花@
We move the stairs, take these walls down,
我移走@些椅子 打掉@些
create an open concept through the kitchen.
搞通向N房的_放空g
There's a gorgeous stained glass here in the corner. The bones are
看看@角落里A的染色玻璃 看@Y
really good.
真棒
When's the part we cough up 12 grand to fix the rotted-out foundation?
那我何r拿出12000美元硇捱@掉的地基
Clearly, it's not for them. Let's just flip this one, El.
很明@@些只能搞定一部分 El
There's a park across the street.
穿^@l街就有一座公@
And the schools here are fantastic if you have a baby.
砟有了孩子@有座W校
When. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Kimmy.
不好意思 什么r候 吉米
When. When you have a baby.
什么r候要孩子啊
We're having a baby. We are having a baby.
我就要有孩子了 我的_有了
You see that? That's called manifesting to the universe.
你知道 @叫宇宙的@F
Sometimes the universe thinks it's funny if I drop $26,000 on in
有r候 宇宙X得我把@26000K拿到外面先扔了
vitro first.
比^有趣
Oh! You're a dick. I'm kidding.
哈 你真 我就_玩笑
If this place is so great, why don't you guys move in here?
如果@里真@么棒 你怎么不搬
What are they gonna do with five bedrooms and a park?
那他怎么面ξP室和一座公@呢
They're obviously never having kids.
很@然他不有
Look at 'em. They don't have any emotional holes to fill.
看看 他可]有什么情感漏洞要填a
Not that we are doing it to fill...
F在我可要a上
Shut up, Russ. All right.
ef了 Russ 好的
What was that look? What look?
干嘛@涌粗我 我怎么了
He just said you guys were never gonna have kids. Then you did a
他才f你不有孩子 然后你
definite look.
很明@是在看我
Yeah, what was the look for? You looked back at me to include me in
是啊 你什么眼神 你后砘仡^
your look.
看著我
I didn't do a look. Totally did a look.
我]看啊 ^看了
It wasn't a look. I think we just started some trouble.
]有 我想我正在制造一些麻
There's no trouble. Maybe even a fight.
能有什么麻 甚至可能要打起砜
There's no fight. There's no trouble. Let's get out of here.
不打起淼 ]有任何麻 我走吧
Oh, my God. You guys are gonna have kids now, aren't you?
天哪 你不是要孩子了吧
No. What? Kimmy. I don't know. What?
]啊 Kimmy 我不明白 你f什么
Of course you are, because you have to win at everything.
你然有了 因槟o如何都要A我
Then you're gonna throw your perfect uterus in my face too.
然后你要拿你完美的子m打我吧
How do you know my uterus is perfect? We've never even tried to have
你怎么知道我的子m很完美 我甚至]有L
kids.
要小孩
I don't know if I can get pregnant.
我都不清楚我是否能言
Of course it is perfect. It is yours.
然很完美咯 因槭悄愕穆
Kimmy. It probably has a leather interior.
嘿吉米 可能有皮革蕊呢
Please, Kimmy. You just got here.
e走 吉米 你才砟
Sorry, Petey. Have a good fight.
Σ黄鹆 彼得 加油吧
See you later, Russ.
下次 拉斯
I didn't do a look. You're doing a look right now.
我]o色 你F在就有
There's no look. You're doing a look.
并]有 你才是在o色
All right, maybe I did do a look.
好吧 可能我是o了色
But just hearing him say it out loud: "We're never having children."
但是到他好大地f 我不有小孩
I mean, is that true?
我意思是 真的
I quit bringing it up because every time I did, you'd say it's not
我不提@事就是因槊看挝艺fr候你都v
the right time.
不是r候
I know, but we were always so broke.
我明白 但我是配合不到一起
And then we were going crazy trying to get the business started.
之后我又得狂 想要重新_始@事
We've flipped five houses this year, and I'm starting to turn down
我今年已看了五套房了 我想_始uu放下
design work.
O的工作
I always thought that I'd be a mom someday.
我是在想我有一天
I think I'm ready. Great. Now you're ready.
我想我浜昧 真棒 你F在又f浜昧
And by the time the kid's 16, I'm gonna be one of those old dads,
然后到孩子十六q 我就是老g父H了
like Brian Hendrickson's dad.
就像布R恩 亨德里克森他爸
Hey, Dad. What's up, Son?
嘿 爸 怎么影 鹤
Hey, Mr. Hendrickson, go long!
嘿 亨德里克森先生 L
Dad?
爸
You killed my dad!
你⑺懒宋依习
Hey. Hey, Dad. Wake up, wake up. Wake up!
嘿 爸 醒醒啊
You did not kill Mr. Hendrickson.
你可]害死亨德里克森桑
And you're not that old.
而且你]那么老
Here's an idea. What if we adopt a five-year-old?
我有c子 如果我收B五q的小孩呢
It'd be like I got cracking when I was 36. How about that?
那我36q也能大干一 如何
Keep your end straight, will you?
保持直Y束可以
Look, you're overthinking it, bro. None of my kids were planned.
兄弟 你想多了 ]哪要孩子是好了的
Kid shows up, you figure it out. Easy-peasy.
想要孩子了 你搞定它 就@么
How many kids you got now, Stu? Number four's in the oven right
你F在有孩子了 斯D 第四快要
Now.
出生了
Wow. Nothing hard about kids.
喔哦 Ω逗⒆]什么y的
As long as you spend some time with them, they're cool.
只要你樗花rg 他就很乖
Most important thing, make sure the moms all get along.
最重要的是和孩子他能和睦共
Meatball. Hey! Hey, buddy!
嘿 肉球
Hey. You miss me?
想我了
Oh! That's my boy. You missed me, huh? I missed you too.
哦 乖孩子 想我了是吧 我也想你
Yeah. You're such a good boy.
真乖
Hey, El. I got the towel samples you wanted for the kitchen.
嘿 艾莉 我弄砹N房用的毛巾悠
El, you okay?
艾莉 你好
Hey, what's the matter?
嘿 怎么了
Nothing. I was just thinking about what you said about adopting a
]什么 我就在想你f的IB一
Five-year-old.
五q小孩
I said that? Yeah.
我有@么f^ 是啊
I was totally... I was joking. I know. It's kind of crazy.
我就是_玩笑 我知道 是有c狂
But it just got me thinking. And there's so many kids in foster care.
但我真的想了想 寄B中心真的有很多小孩
And they're moving from place to place, and they don't have anybody,
而且他常搬戆崛 ]有任何H人
and it's like the saddest thing I've ever seen.
@是最我y^的
I found this adoption agency. They're having an orientation next week.
我找到了@IBC 下周他有介B
No, don't show me that. I don't want to see those little faces.
eo我看@ 我不想看到他的小
You trying to break my heart? I just got home from work.
你想我心 我才工作回砟
Ellie, people who take in foster kids are really special.
艾莉 照@些小孩的是一些很特e的人
These are the kind of people who volunteer when it's not even a
都是些志愿者 甚至]有
Holiday.
假期
We don't even volunteer on a holiday.
我可]有假期做志愿者
What if there was, like, a disaster?
如果有些 嗯 疾的呢
What, like a dirty bomb? Whatever.
那可就像K 那都o所^
And there's a little kid who ends up on our doorstep.
有那些孩子都到我家T口了
Are we gonna turn her away because we're not special enough?
我就要s走他 只因槲不蛱厥
That would depend. There's a lot of factors that go into it.
那就取Q于 那要考]很多因素的
I mean, our food rations, the blast radius.
我是f 我的食物配o以及可接受的范
El, you can't take some offhanded remark I made
艾莉 你不能在意我S便f的
and turn it into a crazy life decision.
然后做出狂地Q定
It was a joke.
那就是一句玩笑
Yeah.
是啊
I know. I just...
我明白 我只是
You're right. You shouldn't be pushed into something you don't want
你是Φ 不能逼你去做
to do.
你不想做的
It was just a nice thought.
那_是好想法
Good night.
晚安
All right, I won't make any more jokes like that.
好的 我不再_那些玩笑了
All right?
行
You wanna watch a little Fixer Upper?
你想看些待修房
Okay, I love you. I love you.
好吧 我勰 我也勰
That's a long fill-up, my friend.
我很空 我的盆友
Well, that's because I wanted you to come in here.
那就是槭裁次蚁肽
We're gonna have a karate kicking contest. Me versus you, straight up.
我隹帐值Q吧 就我跟你 一σ
Oh, God.
哦 天哪
It's not fair. That is not...
@不公平 @真的
Hey.
嘿
You can't buy these pita chips anymore. They're way too spicy.
你可不能再I@些薯片了 太辣了
I'm getting my nose watery and...
辣的我要流鼻涕了
Over a half million children are currently in foster care.
F在有超^五十f的寄B和
The system is overloaded, okay?
系y超d了 知道
It doesn't need any more kids.
不能再接收更多孩子了
So for a child to be removed, conditions have to be pretty bleak,
因此 孩子必得D移 而且生活l件更差
usually involving abuse or extreme neglect.
通常包括虐待或者被O端忽
And some of these kids can often languish in the system,
他中的一些更是得憔悴
unless a wonderful family like yours steps up for them.
除非有更多像你@|家庭的⑴c
We'll step up. We'll take one right away.
我一定⑴c 我F在就要ё咭
Perfect. Let me go check in back, see what we have in stock.
好O了 我F在就去登 看看我的存
She is kidding, of course.
她然是在_玩笑
We do not stock.
我可]有齑
And you know that.
你懂的
But we can take you through the eight-week foster parenting course,
我可以你W八周的收B家庭n程
and you can get your certification.
然后你就得到Y格C
And then we can pair you with some kids that you can foster
然后我就湍c一些寄B孩子配
until they become adoptable.
直到你IB成功
But it is not gonna be easy, folks.
但@可不闻 大伙
These kids will test your will,
@些孩子y你的意愿
put a strain on your relationship,
o你的P系制造毫
and push buttons you didn't even know you had.
一不留神就被淘汰
I can tell by looking at you that not all y'all are gonna make it.
我敢你面f并不是所有人都能做到
I actually think this group has got the grit to face some unpleasant..
事上我想你有勇饷@些不快
Excuse me. Y-You guys heading out?
打_一下 你@就走啦
Yeah. Okay. Well, thank you. Bye-bye.
是 好吧 xx 再
All right, that one's on me. It absolutely is.
好吧 怪我 很明@是的
We've gone over this before. We have.
我之前也有^似v 是的
This is a problem. It's a problem.
是} ]e
Okay, everybody, why don't we learn your names
好的 各位 不如我砹私庀履的名字
and what type of children you're looking for.
以及你中意那N型的孩子
Oh, hi.
哦 你好
We're Dana and Dirk McCann.
我是戴安娜 和 迪克 坎
And the Lord has guided us here
是上帝指引我磉@
to adopt a baby boy... or a girl.
硎震B一小男孩 女孩也行
Yeah, the big guy, he's blessed us with so much. Mm-hmm.
是的 上帝一直在保佑我 嗯哼
We'd just like to share it with a child that needs a home. Yeah.
我就想c孩子分享一家 是的
What about over here?
你呢
I'm David, and this is my wife, Jessie.
我是大l @是我妻子杰西
And we've been trying to have a baby for three years now.
我榱撕⒆右呀努力三年了
But no matter what we do, I... I can't...
但不管我怎么做 我就是不能焉
I'm sorry. Can someone else go? It's okay.
不好意思 能直接到下一位 ]P系
It's okay. Well, I'm Kit and this is Michael.
好的 我是基特 @是~克
We've also been trying to conceive now.
我也在努力要孩子
Pretty much since the first night we met, right?
大概奈第一次面_始 Π
That is correct. We're just not having any luck.
]e 我只是不太走\
We're looking for a child of any gender
我想收B一9q左右的孩子
or ethnicity up to nine years old.
不性eN族
Hello. My name is October Ross Jennings.
你好 我是十月 _斯詹妮斯
And I would like to be the single mother
我想做斡H母H收B一
of an athletically gifted teen boy
有\犹熨x的青少年
who I can help to reach his full Division One scholarship potential.
我能激l他@得全一W金的力
Preferably African-American.
最好是美非混血
Mm-hmm. Right?
嗯哼 好的
Like The Blind Side. Like the movie. Right? That's great.
就像影 弱c 是 真棒
Honey, she's not joking.
H鄣 她不是在_玩笑
A-Are you jo... You're not joking? My God. I'm so sorry.
你是在_玩笑 天哪 Σ黄
I just thought 'cause of the gay guys' conceiving joke that we were...
我以檫在跟著那z基佬的言泄ｉ_玩笑呢
I mean, that is the plot of The Blind Side, so...
我意思是 @是影 弱c 的∏榘
I've never seen it. So, please, it's your turn. Just do not talk to
我]看^ 所以 拜托 到你了
me anymore.
e再f我了
Yeah, she's nuts.
嗯 她lj了
I'm so sorry. I feel terrible. I, uh...
Σ黄 我感X很糟
So, my name's Ellie. Hi. This is my husband, Pete.
我叫Ellie 你好 @是我老公Pete
Uh, yeah, I mean, I'm not too sure about any of this.
~ 是的 我意思是我不是很了解@
I mean, I get it. We adopted our dog Meatball, and we love him like
我是f 我明白 我收B了一只狗 我鬯到
crazy, but...
l狂 但
Don't compare kids to dogs. I'm not.
e拿孩子跟狗比 我]有啊
I'm just saying there used to be a stigma about getting a dog from
我只是f^去游锸杖菟IB狗是一N
the pound,
u辱
but now they're called rescue dogs and everybody wants one.
F在Q作拯救狗狗 而且每人都想要一
Don't say "pound," don't say "dog." Just don't.
e再f 收容所 狗狗 了
Okay, no, that's not...
好的  @并不是
It's just all of this is a little scary, right?
只是有c小心Π
But maybe if you call them rescue kids... Oh, my God.
可能你Q其檎救孩子 哦 天哪
...instead of foster kids, more people would be into it
泶替收B @更多人能容易接受
and people wouldn't walk out in the middle of your seminar
@尤就不在你的研中途x_
and it'd be good for your program. Pete! Pete!
@δ的目更有椭 彼得e
I'm just saying... Just stop it!
我只是f ef了
Oh, everyone, our guest speaker of the day,
看 各位 @是今天的演v嘉e
Brenda Fernandez and her parents.
布m_M南德斯和他的家人
Let's make them feel welcome.
他感受你的崆榘
Hey, thank you.
嘿 xx
Hi.
你好
So, when I was eight years old,
我八qr
my mom and her boyfriend decided it would be a good idea
我和她男朋友Q定
to build a meth lab in our garage.
在我的旖ㄒ蛔制毒工S
They made me deliver drugs for them.
他逼我樗毒
They abused me physically, and some of their customers abused me
他虐待我 有些客人也
sexually.
ξ施性虐待
Uh, when I was 11, our garage exploded,
我十一qr 我的煺了
and I was put in the system,
然后我就到@砹
bounced around from placement to placement.
囊地方到另一地方
Pretty soon I was 14.
很快我就十四了
Nobody wants a teenager, so I'd be aging out in a few years.
]人想要十q的少年 ^啄旮大了
The thing is, over half the kids who age out of foster care
事就是一般的孩子都超^了收B年g
end up homeless, addicted, incarcerated, or dead within two years.
最K就是o家可w 染毒 或者]赡昃退懒
That was gonna be me, trying to start my adult life,
到我了 我L_始我作槌赡耆说纳活
but with no family to help me pick a college,
但]有家庭愿意Y助我上大W
nobody to come home to on the holidays
假日也o家可回
or cry to when my first boyfriend dumped me for Missy Howard.
榈谝蝗文杏雅腿而哭泣
But then those two... very special people came along.
但@晌 非常特e的人出F了
And I didn't make it easy on them.
而我并]有和善的Υ他
But no matter how hard I pushed them away,
但o我如何s他走
they were always there with a sack lunch and a ride.
他是砦顼并我兜L
Thanks, you guys.
xx你
Come here, Daddy. You too, Mama.
到@戆职 有你
That was good.
真棒
I am so sorry about the Blind Side comment.
我橹前P于 弱c 的不言道歉
I love the movie.
我圻@部影
Bye, Brenda. Great job. Amazing. All right, Kit, bye.
再 布m_ 干得不e 很棒 好的 基特 再
Dirk. We'll see you in the classes, buddy. Bye, guys. Hey.
德克 n上再 大伙涸僖
So now you think we're special enough? Maybe we are.
如今 你X得我足蛱厥 可能吧
I mean, this is what we do.
我是f @就是我要做的
We see potential in things, we fix 'em up. Like they did.
我看到事情的在因素 搞定它 就象他
They find this kid in a state of disrepair,
他在@孩子 年久失修 的B中找到她
they give her a new coat of paint, scrape off her emotional popcorn
o她漆上新漆 刮去情感屋的
ceiling,
o用y理
install some countertops in the form of love or self-esteem, whatever.
安b上叟c自尊的工作_
I'm not saying she's a house like the way I said the dog thing in
我并不是f她像一房子 就如我形容狗
there,
那
but I think we're perfect for this.
但我想我很m合做@拥氖
But she's really... she's not a house, Pete.
但她真的 他不是一幢房子 彼得
I just said she's not a house. Are you listening to me? Okay. No,
我f了她不是房子 你在我f 然
I am.
然在
I'm so exci... Are you excited?
我很d^ 你呢
I just get worried
我就是有c心
that you think things are gonna be easier than they actually are.
事情真的跟你想的那雍
What? I do not. You do.
什么 我]f啊 你f了
This whole thing was your idea. Now I'm pumped about it, and you're
整件事都是你的想法啊 我F在嗨到不行
not?
而你s不激
No, no, I am pumped. Well, you don't look pumped.
不不 我有嗨到 是 看起砜刹幌
A big, life-altering moment like this, you gotta get pumped.
面@右改你生活的重要r刻 你表F得更嗨
We're about to do something insane.
我z可是要去干件狂的大事呢
Did you hear her speak? Yes.
你有她f什么 然
It was the greatest thing I've ever heard. I know.
那是我@子到的最的 我知道哦
Come on, cowgirl, let me get a "yee-haw." Yee-haw.
戆 女牛仔 跟著我f
No, bull. Gimme one. Yee-haw!
不是@  跟我W  咦哈
Louder. Crazier. Come on. Come on! You're about to be a mom!
大c  狂c  快c  你都快要成橐了
Yaaa-hoo!
咦哈
Add a balloon, El.
填馇  艾
Okay, have a seat.
好的  坐下吧
Time's up.
rg到了
These are your fantasy kids.
@些是你幻想中的孩子
They are not your real children.
不是你真正的孩子
Come on, Jessie. You're losing her.
加油  杰西  你快失去她了
Pete. Pete, Pete! Ticktock, muscle man.
彼得 彼得 彼得  滴答滴答  肌肉男
That's not gonna bring him back from that peanut butter sandwich you
@不能蜃你奈菇o他的花生u中
fed him.
救回他
Your real kids will be very different. Can't erase 'em.
你真正的孩子非常不一  不能擦除他的
Good job, Michael.
做的很好  ~克
All right, October.
好了  十月
I'm calling it. Yours is dead.
我宣布  你的孩子去世了
All there?
都在@了
Time to erase these ideals right now.
是r候把@些想法抹除了
Almost done.
R上就好
Almost done. Okay. Okay.
R上就好了  好的  好的
Thank you. Thank you.
xx你
All right, everybody, I want you all to imagine
好了  所有人  我想你O想一下
you got this plush new job.
你得到了一新的舒服的工作
They give you a nice big office.
他o你一又大又好的k公室
There's a gym and a frozen yogurt machine right there in the break
有健身房和冷鏊崮C就在
room.
休息室
I love frozen yogurt.
我O了冷鏊崮
But deep down, you know you're not qualified.
但是刃纳钐  你知道自己不蛸Y格
In your heart of hearts,
你心里深知
you know you're not good enough and you are going to get fired.
你自己不蚝  以后被_除
The same way you got fired from your last three jobs.
就像你之前三次被_除一
And you might quit just to get some control back.
你也有可能主愚o去拿回一些掌控
Hell, you might even tip over that damn yogurt machine
你甚至有可能打翻那死的冷鏊崮C
and walk your ass right on out of there.
然后不要的哪抢镒叱鋈
Just to clarify,
澄清一下
Karen is not advocating vandalism in the workplace.
P不是在倡г诠ぷ鞯牡胤礁闫
The point is, that it's the same...
重c在于  刃母惺苁且拥
for a displaced child...
τ谝被冷落的孩子碚f
who knows... that you don't want her.
他知道你其并不想要他
Except instead of grieving...
除了槭去工作
the loss of a job,
而悲
she's losing her connection
她在失去和所有人和事
with everything and everyone.
的系
But the one connection
但仍有一系
that can remain
存在
is between siblings.
就是同胞兄妹之g的系
Sometimes it's easier for sibs to adjust
有rτ谕胞兄妹碚f更容易去m
because they're not going through it all alone.
因樗不是孤一人的v了生活中的一切
You might want to consider upgrading to a sibling set.
你也S考]去升到同胞兄妹的e
Dirk? Would you consider siblings?
德克  你考]同胞兄妹
The big guy might smile on that.
@大家伙也S笑出
Um, w-we'd have to...
我要去
We'd pray on that. Right, honey. Yeah.
我要去祈\    H鄣  ]e
Pray on it. The big guy wouldn't give you any more than you can
去祈\  那大家伙不o你超^你所能
handle.
掌控的
I beg to differ.
我不敢同
Pete. Ellie. Hey.
彼得  艾利  你好啊
You made it. Hi.
你砹  你好
Just sign in, and take this form with you
砗到  然后е@表格
and write down the name of any kid you meet you might be interested
下任何你到的你可能感d趣的孩子的名字
in.
字幕
Really? That's how this works?
真的  就是@么做的
Yeah, it can feel a little like shopping for kids.
]e  @是有c像I孩子
It's messed up, I know, but the county puts these on
@有些混y  我知道  但是家弄了@些
because they can match a lot of kids and parents quickly.
因樗能快速的配Φ胶芏嗪⒆雍透改
God, look at the big kids over there.
天  看看那的大孩子
Breaks my heart.
我心都碎了
Most folks want nothing to do with teenagers.
大多等η嗌倌瓴桓信d趣
Of course, if you two thought you could make room for an older child..
然  除非你J槟可以o大c的孩子出地方
Um, I mean... I... Oh, God.
不  我的意思是  我  天啊
I'm so sor... We... We're terrible people. I'm sorry.
Σ黄  都是我的不好  Σ黄
You're not terrible. Now get on in there and find you a family. Go on.
不是你的e  F在M去吧  o自己找家  去吧
God, it's so weird.
天啊  @感X好奇怪
Normally, you go out and chat up some random kid in a park and you're
正常情r下  你走出去  和公@鹊娜我庖孩子聊聊天
gonna get arrested.
你被逮捕的
Now we're just supposed to? I know.
我F在就@么做  我明白你的想法
This little guy's all by himself. You want to go say hi?
@小家伙就他自己一人待著  想去打招呼
Yeah. Okay.
是的  ]e
Excuse me. Sorry. So sorry. Occupied. Hey! Sorry.
打_一下  Σ黄  非常抱歉  此孩被占  等下  Σ黄
Occupied! Sorry!
被我占了  不好意思
We just went to get treats. So, yeah, just back it up. Okay?
我只是去Ic|西  你_c  行
Hey, look, we got some snacks. Come on, Lucas, right over here.
看啊  我砹它c零食    R卡斯  磉@
Hey. Excuse me! Heads up!
打_一下  注意
Never mind. Thanks.
]事了  xx
You just take it and try to throw it into his mouth.
你拿住它  然后L把它扔到他嘴里
Really. You want to have a go?
真的  你想碓一下
Oh.
好吧
Nice to meet you.
很高d到你
Get it? Oh, yeah. Bring her in!
抓到了  很好  把她н^
Hey. You gotta wait for your turn, buddy.
等下  你要等著到你  兄弟
I'm sorry. Let's... Let's just go. Let's just go.
很抱歉  ]事  我去e的地方吧
Pete. Ellie.
彼得  艾莉
How's it going? Hey.
最近怎么  你好
Yeah, well... it's a little weird.
好吧  @一c奇怪
Yeah, these things can be kind of awkward.
是的  @些事情是有c擂
But did you meet any kids that you're curious about?
但是你遇任何感d趣的孩子了
We met one little girl who was sitting all by herself.
我碰一自己一人坐著的小女孩
Very sweet, a little guarded. Kind of had a little wall around her.
很可  有c认  好像在周Q起了隔x
Really small for her age too. Maybe a fetal alcohol thing or
τ谕g人碚f她也很矮小  有可能是烟r酒或者
something.
e的什么原因
I saw her... Oh, right there.
我看她  就在那
The little sad-looking one with pigtails
那有悲的扎著p子的小女孩
who seems like she's been chained to a radiator half her life.
看起硐袷谴蟀胼子被一散崞魇`了
Uh, that's my daughter. The radiator kid?
呃  那是我女  那散崞骱⒆
What?
什么
Yeah. That's my daughter.
是的  那是我女
I'm so sorry.
不好意思
You don't have to be sorry. I'm really proud of her.
你不必抱歉  我很樗傲
The reason she's sitting away from others is because she has a family,
她不和e人坐一起的原因是因樗有了一家庭
a very happy family.
一很幸福的家庭
And I didn't drink a drop when I was pregnant. Nor do I have a
而且我言械r候也]碰一滴酒  我也]有一
radiator.
散崞
Of course. You should be really proud. I am.
然  你感到傲  我是的
I'm sick of looking at that. To hell with it. I'm going over there.
我受不了看著那些了  不管了  我要去那了
Pete. Hey, Pete.
彼得  等下  彼得
Pete, what are you doing? Look at them over there.
彼得  你在做什么  去那看看他
Everybody's avoiding them like they're dipped in shit. I'm just gonna
他就像粘^屎一  所有人都避_他  我只是想
go say hi.
去打招呼
Yeah, okay... Hey, Pete, Pete, just wait.
好吧  等下  彼得  等一下
I know. I think it's awful. But they're teenagers, okay?
我知道  我感X@很糟糕  但是他是青少年  明白
They use drugs, and they masturbate,
他吸毒  他打wC
and they watch people playing video games on YouTube.
他在油管W站上看e人玩子游
We're not equipped for that. What do we have to be equipped for?
我]槟切┳龊  那我槭裁醋龊
I'm just going to say hello. I know. I don't think we should do that.
我只是想去打招呼  我知道  我不J槲那么做
Excuse me? Hi. Hey. Hi.
打_一下  你好  你好
Hi!
你好啊
Just FYI, we can all hear you.
只是想告V你一下  我都能的
Hmm? "Dipped in shit."
什么  粘^屎
"Masturbate," so forth.
打wC  @些
Uh, we appreciate the concern, but there's no need to go all pity
我很感x@些P心  但]必要f的@么
crazy.
狂
We know how this works.
我知道@是怎么淼
So just go on. It's okay.
去e的地方吧  ]事的
Go mingle with the kiddies and don't give it another thought, okay?
去和那些小孩子混在一起  不要多想  好
Have a good day, folks. Thanks. Bye-bye.
^得愉快  xx  再
So, you two went out and found yourself a teenager after all, huh?
那么  你出去  是o自己找了青少年
We only met her for a second. But she made a real impression.
我只了酌腌  但是她留下了一很好的印象
Oh, yeah. Lizzy's such a great kid.
是的  是一很好的孩子
She does really well in school. Come on back.
她在W校表F很好  磉@
She came into care four years ago when she was 11.
四年前她十一q的r候就碚疹所了
Took a lot to convince her to accept placement in an adoptive home.
花了很久去裾f她接受安置在一寄B家庭
Her mother... Set the house on fire, passed out with a crack pipe.
她  把房子弄起火了  在裂掉的管子旁倒了
What I was gonna say... Before I told it like it is?
我想f的是  在我f出事之前
Before you jumped on in there,
在你打辔抑前
is that her mother's made a lot of promises over the years
她@啄碓S下了很多承Z
and never seems to follow through with them.
但]有⑺M行到底
Where's her mom now?
她F在在哪里
Probably in an orange jumpsuit selling smokes in the yard.
也S在院子里穿著B衣u著香
I'm sure that's not accurate.
我保C那并不蚀_
Huh. Turns out Lizzy's mom is finishing a sentence in county jail.
最后lF的就在Oz里接受判Q
Who called it, huh? Who said it?
lf^什么  lf^
You did. Yeah.
你f^  好吧
Looks like she's never pursued reunification
看起硭]有砗退的孩子重聚
or contacted her kids in over two years,
也在超^赡]有系^她的孩子
so, yeah, she's pretty much a nonissue.
那么  好吧  她差不多就是o足p重的事
That's terrible. What about the father?
@糟糕O了  那她爸爸呢
What are you talking about, "father"?
你在f什么呢  爸爸
What, are you doing comedy for us now, Pete?
你在o我表演喜  彼得
Karen, we've had plenty of fathers who have stepped up,
P  我有很多站出淼陌职
but in this case, no ID's on any birth fathers.
但是在@里  任何生父都]有名字
Look, Lizzy's mom is a product of the system
著  的是w系下的a物
and she never learned to properly care for herself, much less three
她]W^怎么照好自己  更不要f三
kids.
孩子了
Three? Three kids? Oh. What?
三  三孩子  什么
Yeah, three.
是的  三
Yeah, Lizzy... At once?
是的    一次生下的
Yeah, Lizzy comes with two younger siblings, Juan and Lita.
是的  和她小c的同胞兄妹阮和塔是一起淼
Wait, wait. So we would have... three children?
等等  那我  要I三孩子
No. Two, maybe, but there's no way we can do three.
不  吧  也S  但是我不可能能IB三的
I mean, we wanted to meet... Oh, my gosh.
我的意思是  我曾想去看看  天啊
Why would you show us that? You're an asshole.
槭裁醋我看@  你是混蛋
Why would you even show that? They're so cute. That's wrong.
你槭裁匆我看@  他@么可  @么做不
Listen, we're not gonna sugarcoat it, okay?
J真  我不掩@件事  好
Lita is a... a wild, rowdy kid,
塔是  野U吵[的孩子
and Juan can be fragile and a little emotional,
阮有c脆弱  感情上有c敏感
and Lizzy is strong-willed and she won't trust easily.
意志力很  她不p易信任他人
God, can you blame her? Well, but listen.
@你能怪她  好吧  但是著
We wouldn't recommend this match if we didn't believe
我一般不建h@次配  要不是我相信
that with some structure and love
通^一些造和感情
these... these kids could blossom, right?
@三孩子也S`放出花  明白
Yeah, and we're hoping to get them out of their current foster
是的  并且我希望能蜃他[F在的寄B
placement.
情r
The Muskies might lose that meal ticket. Karen, please.
R斯基一家也S失去@票  P  ef了
Most of our foster parents are really terrific, caring people.
我大多档募酿B父母是很棒的很有同情心的人
And, yes, there are people who do it just for the paycheck.
但_也有些人是榱顺诙做@些
But the Muskies are not abusive or evil.
但R斯基一家并不是虐待或者有害的
Just maybe a little... Inbred.
只是有一c  近HY婚
Karen, there is no evidence to... You've seen 'em.
P  ]有C表明  你^他了
I swear they look like brother and sister. I can't tell them apart.
我l誓他看起硐裥置  我分辨不出他
In any case, I'd love to set up a visitation,
不管怎么f  我很芬獍才乓探L
unless you have any other concerns.
除非你有e的]
It's just a visitation. So...
只是一探L  那么
I-I-It's just... Is it a problem...
只不^  @真的]}
You know, the whole white savior thing?
你知道的  整白色救世主@件事
Like the Avatar thing. Avatar?
就像阿凡_那件事  阿凡_
You know how the blue guys couldn't fight off the unobtanium guys
你知道{色的家伙是怎么]k法敉四切聿傻V的人
until the white guy showed up and pretended to be a blue guy?
直到白色的人出F了并窝b成了一{色的人
All I'm saying is, white-bread couple taking in little Latin kids.
我想f的是  白w色的夫D接{著拉丁小孩
Are people gonna think we shouldn't be doing that?
人不X得我不@么做
You know what? We'll go ahead and toss these kids back into the system
你知道  我重新把那些小孩放回去
and I'll just jot you down for "whites only."
然后o你下  HIB白w色小孩
Come on. I didn't mean... Hey! No, that's not...
不不不  我不是f  等下  不是  @不是
Don't write "whites only." That's not what he meant. That's not
e下  HIB白w色小孩  @不是他的意思  @不是
at all what I meant.
焊不是我的意思
Pete, I appreciate your cultural sensitivity,
彼得  我感激你的文化敏感
but we have every color of kid in the system.
但是我@里收{了各Nw色的小孩
And we have every color of parent. Every color.
我也有各Nw色的父母  每Nw色
Just not nearly enough. Not nearly enough parents.
只是不蚨  -父母盗坎蚨
And listen.
著
You're gonna get some funny looks.
你受到一些奇怪的眼光
And people are gonna say some stupid shit.
人也f些蠢
But if you're willing to love these kids who need a mom and dad,
但是如果你真的喜g@些需要爸爸的孩子
and somebody has a problem with that,
而有人Υ擞挟h
you just ask 'em how many goddamn kids they've adopted.
你只需要他收B了多少的孩子
Exactly. Hell.
]e  f得
I just wanted to have the Avatar talk. Now we did, so I'm good.
我只是想f一下阿凡_  F在我f完了  我]}
Oh, fantastic.
好  棒O了
You ready to meet three kids? Three kids?
你浜萌ヒ孩子了  三孩子
Yeah. All right. We'll set it up.
是的  那好  我安排一下的
Hey. How's it going?
你好  ^得怎么
Uh, good. It's going really good.
很好  ^得很好
Pete and Ellie. Yeah, we know. Come on in.
我是彼得和艾莉  我知道  M戆
Good luck with that one. She thinks she's better than everybody.
希望你能和那孩子^得  她J樗比所有人都好
Yeah. The other two are jackassing around out back.
是啊  另外就在后面e逛
We'll be in the shop.
我去商店
Hey, uh, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner. How are you?
你好  瓦格{夫D  你好
Oh, uh, Ellie and Pete.
叫我彼得和艾莉就好
You don't have to call us the Wagners. No, please. Good to...
你不用叫我瓦格{夫D  不  ]事  很芬
Um, sorry about them. They're... Oh, please.
Σ黄  他  ]事
They just seem a little... Like brother and sister?
他只是有c  像兄弟姐妹
Pipe down with that crap. We are not friggin' related.
管好你的嘴  我不是H戚P系
Friggin' related.
天⒌挠H訇P系
I'm really gonna miss them.
我真的很想念他的
That is, if you... No. Please. Oh, my goodness.
前提是  如果你  不不不  天啊
You made such a good impression on us when we met you,
我第一次面r你o我留下了很好的印象
we wanted to get to know you a bit more.
我想多了解你一c
Yes! Meet your brother and sister.
是的  你的兄弟姐妹
They're right outside, if you guys wanna follow me. Yes! Yes.
他就在外面  如果你想跟著我  是的
Juan. Lita.
阮  塔
I want you guys to meet Pete and Ellie.
我想你彼得和艾莉
Hi. Hey, guys.
你好  嘿  孩子
Are we gonna go stay at your house now?
我F在就要住在你家了
Well, we met your sister, and she's so awesome.
我^你姐姐  她很棒
Yeah, she's really cool. She was telling us about you guys.
是的  她很酷  她正告V我P于你的事
Want to play restaurant with me?
想和我一起去餐d
Yeah, I would love to.
是的  我很芬
Where's your restaurant? Right over there.
你的餐^在哪里  就在那
And what's your doll's name? Her name is Potato Chips.
你的洋娃娃叫什么名字  她的名字叫薯片
I love potato chips. Potato chips are my favorite.
我喜g薯l  薯l是我最喜g的
Nice one.
很好的投球
Can we be the Clippers? I'm more of a Lakers fan.
我能快船  我更喜g湖人
Oh, uh, sorry. You don't have to say sorry. That's okay.
哦  Σ黄  你不需要fΣ黄鸬  ]事的
We can be the Clippers. O-Okay.
我可以快船  好的
I'm gonna shoot, you crash the boards. Yeah. Sure.
我要投球了  你去诎  好的  ]}
You did it on purpose! What?
你是故意的  什么
You hit me 'cause I like the Clippers.
你糁形揖鸵槲蚁g快船
The Clippers are awesome. We love the Clippers. Are you kidding me?
快船很棒啊  我喜g快船  你在_玩笑吧
It was so smart to get rid of Blake Griffin. That was a great trade
[了布雷克 格里芬真是太明了  那是一P很好的交易
for them.
τ谇蜿碚f
We're obsessed with the Clippers. I can't get enough of them.
我O了快船  我都不λ感到
They're amazing. Okay.
他太棒了  好吧
Can we play hide and seek? You sure? You lost a lot of blood.
我可以玩玩捉迷藏  你_定  你流了很多血
I love hide and seek. Okay, but just us. No girls.
我喜g捉迷藏  好吧  但只有我  ]有女孩
Oh. Sure.
哦 好吧
It's not that progressive, but no problem.
有c老套  但]P系
Lita, should we go play restaurants? Yeah.
塔 我去玩^家家吧  好
You're it. I'll hide and you count. Okay?
你戆  我聿啬岛
You sure you're okay? Yeah.
你_定你]事   我]事
Go on, count. Count to 20. All right, buddy.
快c  _始蛋  档20   好的
Oh, my God.
天啊
You better not embarrass me at the restaurant.
你最好e在餐^我下不砼_
Potato Chips has been bad today. Bad girl!
薯l今天特e  呐孩
Bad, bad, bad!
牡  牡  牡
Don't talk back, you little beaner!
e嘴  你U物
Oh! Uh... I don't think that's...
哦 ~  我X得
You know what? She picks up that stuff off the TV.
你知道  她是碾上W淼倪@些|西
Yeah. Oh, don't give me the look.
是的  e@么看我
Let's not call her bad names. Don't tell me how to treat my kid!
不能@诱f她的     不用你教我怎么ξ业暮⒆
You think you're better than me, huh?
你是X得自己做的比我好是
Pete, if you don't want the kids,
彼得  如果你不想要孩子的
I'm not gonna push you into it.
我不逼你的
All right, look.
好吧
I'm gonna be honest with you, all right?
我告V你吧
I don't know, I just thought when we met our kids
我也不知道  我只是J楫遇我的孩子的r候
that it would be like this cosmic connection, you know?
就像冥冥之中有感一 你明白
Like just take one look at them and just know, like when you and me met
就是看一眼就知道是我的孩子  就像我初一情一
Yeah. Totally.
是啊  完全同意
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What, you didn't just know?
哇 哇 哇 你早就@么J榈
Hmm? Oh, my gosh.
-嗯  哦  天哪
What? You heard what I said. You didn't just know?
怎么了  你到我f什么了  你不是才@酉氲
No, I was interested, but, you know, I'm more cautious than you are.
不是啊 我很感d趣  但是 你知道的 我比^慎
Really? Wow. How long before you just knew?
真的  真的  你什么r候@么想的
A couple of months.
月前吧
A couple of months? How many months?
月前  月
Like, four...
差不多 四
Four? ...teen.
四月  十四月前
Fourteen? Oh, my God!
十四月前  天
I knew before we got married, okay? That's the point.
我]Y婚前我就知道了好  @就是}所在
We don't have a year-long engagement on this thing.
在收B他@件事情上我可]Cm一年
If we say "yes," they're in our house next week.
如果我同意的  他下周就搬M
Did you feel a cosmic connection?
你感X到冥冥之中的系了
No, I didn't feel a cosmic connection.
]有  我]有感X到
I felt like I was... I felt like I was babysitting other people's kids
我X得我  我像是在oe人的孩子保姆
I agree.
我同意
With what? With you.
同意什么  同意你f的
With me wanting the kids or not wanting the kids?
同意我想要孩子是不想要孩子
Whatever you want. That's not an answer.
你f的都同意   @算什么回答
Then just give me 14 months to think about it. How 'bout that? Come on
那o我14月我考]一下  怎么
Hi!
嗨
It's not a potluck.
@可不是家常便
All righty.
好了
Honey, put those down for me. Thank you.
H鄣  臀曳乓幌逻@ 多x
All right, come on, everybody.
好了  各位
Honey, come on. Jeez.
H鄣  入座了 天
All right, everybody, hands.
好了  各位  手
Hands, hands, hands. Thank you.
手 手 手  xx
Eyes closed.
]上眼睛
I'm thankful for my beautiful grandchildren,
我很感激有可鄣O子O女
including the... the very lucky kids
包括那非常幸\的孩子
that are soon to be adopted by two wonderful parents.
他即⒈很棒的父母IB
I'm really thankful for that too.
我也X得很感激
That is really inspiring stuff, you guys. Well done.
@是非常值得鼓畹  做的很好
Yeah, about that. Actually, we...
其  P于IB的事  我
Yeah, we've decided together not to move forward with the foster thing
我Q定r不IB了
Yeah, we just realized we hadn't thought it through properly, so...
是的  我意R到我]有好好的考]清楚  所以
Yeah! Jesus Christ. This is great news.
天  太棒了
I mean, we were all being supportive to your faces, but...
我是f  我都是支持你的  但是
Yeah. We all thought you were out of your minds.
我都X得你了才IB孩子
I never said anything, but I'm thankful to hear this.
我什么都]f^ 但是我真的很高d到你f不IB了
What? Why?
啥  槭裁
Ellie, let's not. We're holding hands. No, no, no, no.
艾莉  e@  我恐手呢   e e e
I would be thankful to know why you all have a problem with this.
我很感激你槭裁@件事有意
Hey, I never had a problem with it. I think it's smart.
嘿 我Υ送耆]意  我X得很明智
Have a couple kids without the pregnancy and the hormones and the rage
不用言]有荷蒙失{]有情w失控就有孩子
Stop talking. Ellie.
]嘴   艾莉
All I'm saying is that we're thankful
我是f我很感激
that you and Peter are gonna experience
你和彼得v槿烁改
having the love of your own beautiful children rather than...
疼勰H生的可鄣暮⒆ 而不是
Rather than what, Jan? Just spit it out. Hell, I'll say it.
而不是什么    你f出  我碚f
Rather than just rolling the dice
而不是去收B什么
with the offspring of some criminal or drug addict.
罪犯或者a君子的孩子
To be honest, we were worried about our real kids' safety...
f  我很心我孩子的安全
What? ...were they to hang out with your kids, if they're...
啥  孩子一K出去玩  f一你IB的孩子是
Damaged goods?
次品
When I was growing up, a lot of people thought I was damaged goods too
我L@么大  也有很多人J槲沂谴纹
Pete, we're not talking about you, man.
彼得  我不是在f你的
We're talking about crack babies and kids who have been sexually harassed.
我f的是那些有^性}_的孩子
"Sexually harassed"? What do you mean? Their parents made lewd comments?
性}_    你什么意思  他的父母使他生聿豢
You know what I mean, wiseass. Open your stupid eyes.
你知道我在f什么  自作明      _你的狗眼吧
How long have everyone's eyes been open? Kimmy, you of all people.
大家什么r候都_眼了  吉米 有所有在座的各位
What if you can't have a baby? Do not put that out into the universe, please.
如果你不能生孩子呢 e把@N假O放在所有人身上
What if you can't? What are you gonna do?
如果呢  你怎么k
If you don't quit being so nuts about this baby thing,
你要是再因楹⒆拥氖卤票
I swear to God, I'm gonna get pregnant again this afternoon
我l誓 我下午就言
just to spite you.
就榱盒哪
And you know I can do it. Really?
你知道我能做到的  真的
No. Oh.
假的  哦
I'm sorry if we're not as politically correct as you guys,
如果我的立龈大家不同  那很抱歉
but our baby has to be our blood.
但是孩子身上必流著我的血
Yes! Absolutely! Oh, my God. "Our blood."
是的 必是 我的天 “我的血”
This blood? This blood right here? What's that supposed to mean?
@血  在@的@血  那是什么意思
Jerry, what do you think about this? I'd be thankful if we could eat, Russ.
杰瑞  你f呢   有吃我已很感激了  拉斯
You just spent 30 minutes talking about the deep state.
你花了三十分家大事
You don't have an opinion on your own family?
自己家的事你不管了
None of my business. Thank you, Daddy.
不P我的事 多x 老爸
I would like you all to know that thousands of children
我想告V你成千上f的孩子
are spending Thanksgiving without any family at all.
根本]有家人一K^感恩
And right now I kind of envy them. But I know you guys love me.
但是F在我有cw慕他了  我知道你畚
I know that I have a place to go to eat turkey and be thankful.
我知道我有地方吃火u  我很感激
But a lot of kids don't have that.
但是很多孩子]有
And it's not their fault! And they're not damaged goods!
@根本不是他的e 有他不是次品
So forget what I said before. It is back on!
所以我收回我f的 我是收B的
If that's okay with you, honey. Yee-haw, baby.
如果你]意的 H鄣   咦哈
Yee-haw. We're gonna adopt a whole shitwhack of kids.
咦哈  我就是要收B@些孩子
And I am thankful that whoever has a problem with it can fuck right off
l他有意可以L蛋了  感激不M
Amen. Amen.
阿T  阿T
Well, there goes another Thanksgiving.
好了 又一感恩
You're crazy.
你太酷了
Hi, honey. Here we are.
嗨 H鄣 我回砹
Come in, look around.
M砜纯
This is Meatball.
@是肉球
A Christmas tree?
圣Q
Does that mean Santa comes here?
@意味著圣Q老人
Yeah, every year. Yay!
是啊 每年都  耶
So, you guys are rich. What? Ri... No.
所以  你很有X  有X 不
We're not rich. I mean, we're doing okay.
我不是很有X的  就好
Well... When we got this house, it was a dump.
搬淼r候@里是垃圾
That's what we do. We renovate houses. Ellie did all the design work.
我翻新了@房子  艾莉全程O
Actually, everything is from swap meets and flea markets,
H上  所有|西都是呐f集市和跳瘙市鲑I淼
and it's not that expensive at all.
一c都不F
That's crystal! Sorry. Oh, my God. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
那是水晶 不好意思 天    Σ黄Σ黄
I'm so sorry. Uh, I shouldn't have left this out.
很抱歉  我不把@放在外面的
You guys want to see your rooms? Come on. Let's go check out your room
你想去看看自己的房g 走吧 我去看看你的房g
Lookit! A bed and a bunny! What do you think?
快看啊 小床有小兔子  你X得怎么
I love the bunny 'cause she has a skirt.
我喜g@小兔子因樗穿著裙子
Whose toys are these? They're yours to share.
@些玩具是l的  @些都是你的
Yeah.
是的
Lego!
犯
Can I put my bears in there?
我能把我的熊放那幔
Sure. Of course.
然了 然可以
Wow, you have a lot of teddy bears. These are just court bears.
哇  你有好多泰迪熊啊  @些是法庭熊
They get one every time we go to family court.
我去一次家庭法庭就有一熊
Can you help me? Yeah.
你能拖挛  可以啊
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Look at this, Lita.
哇 哇 哇  你看@ 塔
Lizzy, want me to show you your room?
我你去你的房g吧
Okay. Yeah. It's just here.
好啊  就在@
I'm so sorry you have to carry all your stuff in these awful bags.
很抱歉你用@些塑料袋b行李
If we knew... No, no, it's cool.
如果我知道的 不不不 ]P系的
Fun fact: that's actually how you can spot a foster kid.
有趣的是 H上可以以此判嗍遣皇且IB的孩子
The kid carrying her whole life in a Hefty bag.
@N孩子一子都е大袋子
It's a foster joke.
@是IB圈的玩笑
Well, make yourself at home.
在家你就S意c
Yeah, this is your place. You can do whatever you want with it.
是啊  @是你的地P  你想怎么佣伎梢缘
Do you wanna put posters on the wall, you wanna paint it?
想在ι腺N海  涂色
Yeah. Come on, This is what we do. We can knock that out in 20 minutes.
是啊  @我可以兔  20分搞定
We can run down to the hardware store, pick any color you like. What do you say?
去下面的五金店  挑你喜g的色 你f呢
Any color. Just pick a color.
任何色都可以  你自己挑
what color do you like?   Any color you want
你喜g什么色   什么色都可以的
Anthing you want
你想怎佣伎梢
You pick a color, we're doing it. You'd look great in green.
你挑色  我刷上  你好像挺喜gG色的
Yeah.
天
What do you think?
X得怎么
Wow, uh, it's, yeah, darkest of the black tones.
哇  ~  有c像最黑的那Nr石的色
Yeah, that's what she picked. Dark Kettle Black, huh?
是的 就是她x的色  -深睾  是
I like it. It's really... dope.
我喜g  酷懒
I'm gonna get dinner started. Okay.
我得去渫盹了  去吧
She doesn't like it. I think she loves it.
她不喜g@色  我X得她超圻@色
Well, you know her better than I do.
好吧 你比我了解她
Hey. Hey, you all done in there?
嘿  嗨 你那弄好了
Oh, yeah. And... she loves it.
弄完了  她超喜g
Oh, great. I'm so glad that she loves her black bedroom.
哦 太好了 她喜g那黑色的P室那我就放心了
So, I'm gonna register Juan and Lita at Harding in the morning.
明天早上我阮和塔去哈丁登
And then you can take Lizzy to the high school.
你去高中
Did you see their shoes? We might want to take them to the mall tomorrow.
你看他的鞋子了]  我明天得他去趟商
Hey, kids, dinner!
孩子  吃了
What? That sounds insane coming out of your mouth.
什么  哪阕炖镎f出砗直不可思h
Do we have kids? Yeah, three of 'em.
我有孩子了  然了 是三
That's insane! I don't believe it!
太酷了  直不能相信
Did you not know that? 'Cause they're really here.
你不知道  他就在@里啊
Holy shit. Holy shit. Yeah. Yeah.
天  天  是真的
They're here. I love you.
他就在@里呢  我勰
What? Kiss again! Kiss again!
怎么了  再H一下  再H一下
God. Mmm!
天
What about that one? Kiss again! Kiss again!
@怎么  再H一  再H一
It's gonna be long and weird.
那很L很奇怪的
How 'bout that? How 'bout that?
可以了吧  好了吧
Come on, giggly. Sit down. I'm gonna shift the plates.
-快c  傻笑的小姑娘  坐  -我去QP子
Great. We have everything. We have burgers and pasta and... Can
好了  好多好吃的  有h堡 意面 有
we have potato chips?
可以吃薯l
Let's get ready for the tub.
湎丛璋
Uh, you two, come on. Who wants to...
你  l想
Hey!
嘿
That's not really a bath toy.
那真的不是洗澡的玩具
I don't want this.
我不想要@
Oh, no! That's gonna... What? Hey! Hey!
e e  那 怎么了 嘿 嘿
I'm gonna get a hamper next time.
我下次得弄固定器
Hey, next time...
嘿  下次
You need...? Lookit!
你需要  你看
Grab... Hold it. Keep it over the sink, please.
抓 抓牢 e它沉下去
Did you flush, sweetie?
_水了
Good night, kiddo. Good night.
晚安  孩子   晚安
Good night!
好
Should we give them a kiss good night? I don't know.
我是不是o他晚安吻的   我也不知道
Maybe you should ask, or should we wait? Should I ask?
要不你去或者我等  我去下
I'll ask. You guys are overthinking this.
我去   你可以直接M砼
Sorry, guys. Sorry.
不好意思  不好意思
Good night. Good night.
晚安  晚安
Good night!
晚安
Should we kiss Lizzy good night?
那我是不是也o晚安吻
I'm good. Good night. Oh. Night, kiddo.
我就不用了  晚安  哦 晚安 好孩子
All right. Good night.
好的 晚安
We try so hard to engage with him,
我已很努力m他了
but no matter what we do, Jake just wants to hang out in his room,
但是不管我怎么做  杰克就只是呆在他的房g里
talking on his phone, swearing, taking the Lord's name in vain,
打 fK {咒R人
and cranking his explicit music till all hours.
[弄音 一待一整天
And he got into another fight at school.
又在W校打架
Thank heaven he didn't seriously hurt one of the other kindergartners.
好]有重幼@的其他小朋友
I think maybe it's okay for a five-year-old to have a cell phone.
五q的小孩子有手C倒是]什么
But does he have a lot of contacts?
但是他有很多系人
We tried to take it, but his birth mother gave it to him,
我D看下的 但是那是他H生o他的
and if we touch it, it's just... Mmm.
我一碰 就 嗯
I'm so sorry. You are so right.
很抱歉  你f的太α
He doesn't need a phone.
他根本不需要手C
We're gonna try again. Definitely try.
我再的 然要
Okay, and Pete and Ellie took in three children ten days ago,
好了  彼得和艾莉十天前ё吡巳孩子
one of which is a teenager.
有十q的
Yeah, it's going pretty good.
是的 一切利
I think our kids made us realize just what kind of a rut we were in before.
我的孩子我意R到我之前的生活有多o聊
Not really a rut. Just the same old routine. You know?
不是f多o聊  就是一成不 你明白
Work, go to the gym, grabbing dinner, drinks, the movies.
上班  健身  吃  喝水  看影
You know what I mean. No, we don't know.
你明白我在f什么  不  我不明白
I think she's just trying to say that we needed a new challenge,
她是在f我之前的生活需要挑
maybe something to break up the monotony.
需要打破@N握{的生活
That's not the only thing they're gonna break.
但是孩子打破的不只是握{的生活
I know it sounds... I know everyone's going through tough stuff.
我知道起  我知道我每人都要v些痛苦
But these kids, I think they're really good. We got lucky.
但是@些孩子  我X得他非常好 我很幸\
They got lucky. Yeah, you hit the jackpot, lady.
是他比^幸\ 是的，你中彩票了
Guys.
大家e@
Why is this funny?
有@么好笑
I think they might be recognizing a little bit of a honeymoon period.
我猜他可能是有c想到度蜜月的r候砝假了
No, we thought of that. But it doesn't feel like a period.
不不  是有c像  但是不像是砝假
Well, I mean, it's not perfect.
我是f也并不是完美的
Lita won't eat anything but potato chips.
塔只吃薯l
But we got a plan to work on that too. I'm not saying we're perfect
我正在想k法解Q  我是f我也不是完美的父母
parents.
真的
And I think I might be recognizing a little bit of jealousy.
我怎么出硪稽c嫉妒啊
It's not a good trait, guys.
各位  @可不是好F象
Okay, what do we have here?
我在@干嘛呢
Huh? Christmas!
啊  ^圣Q啊
What is it? It's a sewing machine! What do you think?
@是啥  pxC  你X得怎么
No? She doesn't like it? Why not?
不好 她不喜g 槭裁窗
Looks like a robot, buddy! Lita, look at this big box!
看著像C器人啊 老弟  塔  你看@大箱子
Dude, it walks and talks. This could be my helmet!
哥  它f走路  @可能是我的^盔
What about the presents? I would've went crazy if I got a robot.
那@些Y物呢   我要是有C器人我高d的
I'm playing with that robot. And this could be the spaceship.
我玩那C器人   @可以宇宙w船
Can I go inside? Sure.
我可以M去  然可以
Hey, guys. Wow, you really like cardboard boxes, huh?
嘿，孩子，哇，你真的很喜g玩箱  哈
Is anybody interested in playing with the giant dollhouse it took
有人喜g@花了三小r弄好的玩具屋感d趣
three hours to assemble?
花了我三小rMb
Did it come in a big box?
是b在大盒子里的
Yeah, it did. It came in a big $200 box.
是的  在一值200美元的大盒子里
Let's go! Let's go!
我走
Come on. Let's go get the box.
戆  去拿箱子了
Christmas is boxes. Yes.
圣Q就是要玩箱子  ]e
Hey, Lizzy, this one's for you too.
嘿    @是o你的
Merry Christmas. Oh.
圣Q快  哇哦
Another one. Yeah.
另一  是的
Thanks. Merry... Merry Christmas.
xx  圣Q  圣Q快
You didn't have to get all this stuff for us.
其]必要o我@么多
I know, I know, but we wanted to.
我懂  我懂  但我很芬
We were excited. Did we go overboard?
我很d^  是不是太^了
No, no, no! Um, I'm sorry.
]  ]  ]  呃抱歉
I'm happy. I am. I...
我很_心
It's nice to see Lita and Juan get presents
很_心看到塔和阮能收到
that weren't donated from total strangers, so...
不完全是陌生人捐的Y物
Hey, Lizzy, if you ever want to talk about anything...
嘿    如果你想聊一些事
I know it's Christmastime and you may have memories and things.
我知道F在是圣Q  你v^些事情
Oh, no, no, no. I'm... I'm...
不不不  我
I'm good. I...
我很好
You know what? I just haven't had my morning coffee yet.
你知道  我只是早上忘喝咖啡了
So I'm gonna get that.
我F在去喝一杯
Do you want some coffee? Sure.
你要  好
We want to thank the Lord for our first Christmas together.
感x上天我一起度^第一圣Q
And we want to give thanks for this lovely meal and also this, um,
感恩碛羞@美味的晚  有
bounty of super fun cardboard boxes.
@些超有意思的板盒子
Amen. Amen.
阿T  阿T
Okay. Tuck in, everybody.
好了  大家_影
Where's my potato chips?
我的薯片呢
We're not having chips tonight, munchkin. Sorry.
今天晚上]有薯片吃  抱歉小家伙
I want my chips. Lita!
我要吃薯片  塔
Pete and I worked really hard on this dinner.
彼得和我很努力地做了@D
There's lots of yummy food for you to eat.
有很多好吃的o你吃
No! Hey, hey, hey.
不要  嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey! Lizzy, Lizzy, please! Lizzy, no, okay? I've got this.
等等    e@  我
Why are you yelling at me? I'm just trying to help you.
你槭裁ξ液  我想湍惆
I'm not yelling at...
我]有吼你
I'm sor... I am. Just then I was. But it's... Look.
呃我的_有吼  Σ黄  但是
Lita, don't do what Lizzy said. What did you say? C uatro? "Go to
塔  不必f的  呃你f了什么
your bedroom"?
回房g
No, cuatro means "quart." Like quart of milk.
不  @~意思是夸  就像一夸牛奶
She said, "You're not gonna have a potato chip, but you will drink
她f  ]有薯片吃  但你可以喝
that milk."
牛奶
In any case, we have this. It's fine.
之  我可以
Okay. Fine. Okay.
好吧  行  好
Let's try some of this meat loaf, okay?
L一下肉吧  好么
No! I want my chips! You're not having chips!
不要  我要薯片  ]有薯片o你吃
I don't think she's getting on board with the plan, honey.
我X得她不你的
I don't want this! Hey!
我不要@  嘿
You sure you don't wanna give her chips? No, we're not giving her chips.
你_定不o她c薯片  不  不o她的
Lita, stay right there!
塔  回
Oh, God, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我天  Σ黄  抱歉
No, it's okay. Don't cry. Relax.
]P系  e哭  放松
Watch your feet, okay? Raised feet!
心_下  抬_
I didn't mean to. I'm so sorry.
我不是故意的  真的Σ黄
You give those to me.
把薯片o我
Ow! Ow. Calm down. Don't cry.
嗷  冷o  e哭
I want my chips!
我要吃薯片
Just stay there, Juan.
e  阮
These are really, really good potatoes.
@土豆真的很好吃
Oh, my God. Are you okay? Oh, God. Hold on.
我的天  你好  我天  等下
Lita, duck!
塔  我去
What are you doing? Look, I'm trying to put it out!
你在做什么  我在想k法缁鸢
With ketchup? Put it out!
用番茄u  缁
All right. Lita?
好了  塔呢
Wait, wh-what's that noise?
等下  什么音
Why is she growling? That wasn't in the classes. I got nothing for
她槭裁催@  上的n里]有教@
that.
怎么k
She's got a knife.
她拿了刀
It's just a SpongeBob knife. It's still a knife.
只是海d的刀  那也是刀啊
Just put the knife down, honey.
把刀放下
Look, kid, just put down the weapon, okay?
孩子  放下武器  好
You guys want me to deal with this, or do you still got it?
你想我硖理  是你依f可以
Do you wanna let her jump in here now, please? Okay, okay. Fine.
她兔Π  好  好好好吧
Fine!
行
Gracias.
xx
Ellie, you gotta learn some Spanish.
艾莉  你得W一c西班牙Z
Why would you give a kid milk in a glass cup? I'm sorry. I didn't.
小孩喝的牛奶槭裁从貌ＡПb  Σ黄  我]
Why did she do that? I hate her!
她干嘛@  我她
That didn't take long. They hate us already.
才]多久  他已我了
Well, technically, she said she hates you.
呃  _切地f  她是f你
Okay, okay, okay! I want a Barbie!
好好好  我要芭比
This isn't even a real Barbie.
@都不算是真的芭比娃娃
You've got a real Barbie that Santa gave you a few weeks ago.
之前圣Q老人都o了你一真的芭比了
Santa got me a fat Barbie! I want a skinny Barbie!
圣Q老人o我的是胖的芭比  我要一瘦的
She's not fat. She's body positive.
她不胖  那是健康的身材
If you put the doll back, I'll get you a giant ice cream sundae.
如果你把娃娃放下  我o你I超大的圣代吃
So you're rewarding this behavior?
所以你是在钏@行
What are you thinking? You handle it.
你在想什么  你硖理吧
Juan, get out of there. Please? Don't hit me! Don't hit me! I'm sorry!
阮  出戆珊  e打我  e打我  我e了
I didn't hit him, okay? I never have hit him.
我]有打他  好  我]打^他
I would never hit a kid. I want a Barbie!
我不打孩子的  我想要芭比
Stop right now, or you're not getting lunch or dinner.
停下  不然]有午也]有晚吃
We're not starving people here, okay? I have this under control.
我不是要l挨I  好  我硖理
Yeah, Lizzy, you body-positive whore!
嘿  你胖婊子
Okay, you're done. Gimme that. Give it to me. Just give me that now!
你完了 o我  把它o我
Oh, yeah? Yeah, it really looks like you've got it.
噢  看起硪磺斜M在你掌握呢
Scan it! Hurry! No! We're not doing this!
哌M去  快c  不  我不要@
Someone videotaping this? Pete, where are you? Where's Pete?
有人下砹  彼得  你在哪里  彼得人呢
You're done. Oh, great. You're out there? Thank you so much.
你完了  行你出去了  真是太感x了
Hey, sweetie. I brought the car.
我把_砹
Saved you a little walking time. We had a front space.
省你走路的rg  T前有路要走
Well, it's still closer.
好吧  但也很近了
Hey, Pete, look at my pretty new doll. Wow.
嘿  彼得  看@新娃娃漂亮吧  哇哦
So you caved, huh? No, I did not cave.
所以你是妥f了  ]有
I bought it for her. It was only four bucks.
我Io她的  只要四美金
Can we just get out of here, you coward?
我能x_@里了  你小鬼
Holy shit. There they are.
P槽  他砹
Hey, Jan, Jerry. They're here.
嘿    杰瑞  他到了
Oh, man! Kid dinged a Porsche.
噢我天  T蹭到了保r捷
Dude, what are you doing? I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
伙你在做什么  Σ黄  Σ黄
All right. Just don't cry, okay?
好吧  e哭  好
He's gonna have to leave a note.
他需要留l了
Just help get the stuff out of the back. Lita! Lita! Honey.
就臀野|西拿出  塔  塔
Ellie looks dehydrated. She looks bad.
艾莉看起硐衩水了  看起砗茉愀
We've got the pizza! Juan, whoa, whoa. What are you doing, bud?
我Я诵┡_  阮  你在做什么
Oh, sorry! Oh, Christ.
噢Σ黄  噢天啊
It's so warm. Hey, put the pizza down.
好暖和  嘿  把披_放下
You can't hold it like that. Hi, Mom.
你不能那幽弥  嗨
Hey, Dad.
嘿  爸爸
You must be Lizzy.
你一定就是
Yeah, hi. I'm Lizzy. Um, this is Lita and Juan.
恩  嗨  @是塔和阮
Hello, Lita.
你好  塔
Hello, Juan.
你好  阮
I'm Grammy "Hw-an" and this is Grandpa "Hw-erry."
我是外婆  胡恩  @是外公  胡瑞
Mom, can you just talk like a normal person?
可以正常cf
I like the way she says her J's.
我喜gJ的l音
Can you please? It's sophisticated.
拜托  很高
Here you go, brother. Thanks, man.
o你  xx
I can't get over it. They look just like normal kids.
我不敢相信  他就和正常孩子一
What did you think they were gonna look like? Little pirates?
你X得他看起像什么  小海I
I don't know. They're just so cute.
不知道  他太可哿
How is the new school?
新W校怎么
It's good. It's like... It's, um... It's school.
挺好的  就像  呃  就像W校
Yeah. Awesome.
哇  很棒
And what's the boy situation? Anything exciting?
那男朋友呢  有]有心
No, no. Hey, hey, leave her alone.
ee  e┧了
She doesn't like talking about that kind of stuff, so just go easy.
她不喜g@些
What? You don't.
怎么  你不喜g的
Actually, there's this one guy, Jacob. Yeah?
其是有叫雅各布的男生  是
Wow, that's a cute name. Jacob. I like... Like Jake.
哇哦  很可鄣拿字  雅各布  我挺喜g的杰克
No, honey, it's "Hway-cob."
不不  是胡各布
Right? Right? "Hway-cob."
胡各布
No, no, it's just Jacob.
不  不  就是雅各布
Yeah, and he's not cute.
Χ且他不是可鄣母杏X
He's more of like an artsy, old soul type.
是cg庀⒌某墒祛型
I was never into the cute ones either.
我也矶疾幌g可坌偷
Nah. Cute's overrated.
恩  可鄄辉趺春
Right? I didn't either. I've never had a hot boyfriend, ever.
是的  我也不喜g  我]有交^性感的男朋友
Shut up!
]嘴
? You look like a monkey ?
?  你看起砭拖裰缓镒  ?
? And you smell like one too ?
?  你起硪蚕袷呛镒  ?
Lizzy, can we put the phone away while we're at the table, like we
桌上可以把手C放下
talked about?
像我之前f的那
Lizzy, please. Give her the phone.
放下  把她手Co我
Hey, guys, check it out. There's some shit going down. Lizzy, the
嘿朋友快看  那有好蚩
phone.
手C
Now.
o我
Is that her real mom? Yeah, that's a harsh move.
那是她的H生母H  好狠的一招
Actually, if you read your foster parent regs,
H上  如果你看了福斯特的育t
you know you're not allowed to take away any of my personal property,
拿走任何私人物品是不被允S的
so...
所以
It's the look. She's doing the look. I gotta get some ketchup.
@表情  就是@表情  我要去拿c番茄u
Pete, you'd said you'd say something to her next time she acts all bitchy.
彼得  你f^下次她再@么^分你采取行拥
I never said the word "bitchy." It was her word, not mine.
我]f^婊膺@次  是她f的  不是我
I am always the bad guy because you're never there.
因槟矶疾辉  每一次我都是那娜
I'm not gonna apologize for working.
我不因橐工作而道歉
Somebody's gotta deal with that dump of a house you bought before it
要有人在你I的房子我破a前
bankrupts us.
搞定它
I bought? You loved it too. And that's not even the point.
我I的  你也喜g啊  而且那根本不是PI
The point is, when you are there, you let them get away with murder.
PI是你在F  你任他各N逍b法外
I got on Lizzy just last night when she wouldn't clean up after
昨晚吃完不肯清理@c
dinner!
我就管教了她
Perfect parent, huh?
完美爸
Is this funny, Kit? I think we're all enjoying this a little bit,
@很好笑  基特  我J槲都X得挺有趣的
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's okay.
Σ黄  抱歉  ]P系
I never get tired of watching white people fight.
看白人吵架我目床
Nor do I.
我也是
But why don't you calm down
但是槭裁床焕潇o一下
and tell us, without blaming each other, what the main issues are.
除了互相怪  告V大家  PI的}是什么
Well, Lita is just constantly...
好吧  塔一直
I want... I don't want to!
我要   我不要
And Juan just doesn't use his head.
阮不肯铀的X子
Unlock the window! And if I say anything about any of it...
解i下窗  而且如果我要f些什么
I'm so sorry. It's not my fault.
我真的很Σ黄  不是我的e
Lizzy's favorite pastime is just... Just leave me alone!
最壅f的就只是  e管我了
Thanks for making me late.
xx我t到
You're an asshole.
你是混蛋
God forbid we actually try to parent the little ones. No, no, that's
我著教育小的  不  那可是
her territory.
她的I地
Don't forget, when Lizzy was ten her mother would disappear for weeks
e忘了  十qr  她的r不r就消失
at a time,
Y拜
leaving Lizzy to parent Juan and Lita all by herself.
留下自照阮和塔
Yeah, she's not just gonna step aside and let you two take over.
她不袖手旁^你z全嘭
Are you saying that we should let her parent the kids? Are you
你是f我她碚疹小的  你有
paying attention?
在
She's 15. She's a terrible parent. She needs to be a kid.
她只有15q  是糟糕的家L  她需要成楹⒆
Now, you gotta step up and become the parents.
F在你要站出砼力成楦改
But you just said she won't let us. Nope, she won't.
但你f她不我  是的她不
You know, Karen, you've been a godsend through most of this,
你知道么  P  大多登r下你都很好
but you're just about to piss me off!
但我F在快被你惹懒
You won't get anywhere with her until you two get on the same page.
情r不改直到你_成共R
Right? That's right.
是  ]e
If she's hostile with you again, maybe try using the three R's.
下次她再表F得不友善  一下三R法t
Okay? Number one: regulate.
第一l  控制情w
"Lizzy, why don't you take some deep breaths, count to ten."
不如档绞  深呼吸
Number two: relate.
第二l  拉近距x
"I understand that you're upset. Nobody likes to feel this way."
我明白你很y受  ]有l愿意v@些
That's good. Number three: reason.
很不e  第三l  f明理由
"Lizzy, it's okay to be angry.
生馐钦常的
What's not okay is to threaten to slash our throats
但是威{要在深夜我睡著r
in the middle of the night when we're asleep."
o我脖子硪坏毒筒辉趺春昧
I'm sorry, did I...?
抱歉  我是不是
That was actually us.Our story.
@是H上  我的故事
Yeah. Last session.
]e  上一次提到的
The little guy didn't follow through with it though.
但小家伙]有猿忠@么做
Well, not yet! Not yet.
r]有  -r]
Sorry, but we shouldn't be laughing.
抱歉  我不笑
No, it's actually important to have a sense of humor about this kind of thing
不  H上碛羞@拥挠哪感也是重要的
Right. You gotta laugh or you'll never make it through this.
]e  多笑笑  不然o法挺^去
That is right.
是的
Speaking of which, next up we have October,
f到@  下一位到W克托布
who still hasn't been matched with a child.
]有和孩子配Τ晒
Well, there's some good news.
K于是有些好消息
So, together we're all gonna decide which chore we'd like to do
我一起Q定哪部分家
and then each week we'll mix it up.
每周再Q
Can I do "Feed Meatball"? Yes!
我可以  喂米堡  可以啊
I want to feed Meatball! You can feed him next week.
我想喂米堡  你可以下周喂他
Pete, I hope she's not serious about all this.
彼得  我希望她不是J真弄@些
It's not just she, it's we. And we are. Very serious.
不只是她  是我  并且我是f真的
Okay, so do you want us to wash your feet too? Oh, Lizzy.
好吧  所以你是想我湍洗_  不
This is bullshit! Lizzy! Hey, hey, wait, wait!
都是狗屁    嘿  等一下
Lizzy. Let's just... Let's... Let's try something else.
我  些e的
Can we just take a moment, calm down, and take a few breaths?
我休息下  冷o下  深呼吸
Please?
好
Try it.
看
Nice! Nice. And we hear you that you're frustrated with the chart.
很好  很好  我明白你@些感到很oZ
Well, yeah. Yeah, I'm frustrated.
]e  我X得很oZ
Yes! And that's okay to be frustrated! We're all frustrated.
是的  oZ很正常  我也都有c沮
So let's think about next time how we can express ourselves better.
我想想下一次怎么更好表_自己
Okay. Okay. Well...
好好  好吧
I don't know, maybe next time you guys...
我不清楚  或S下次你
try and use the three R's on me.
ξL一下三R法t
I could barf all over the ground because it's so nauseating!
我可以吐一地  因樘盒牧
I knew it wasn't gonna work with her.
我就知道@λ]用
Oh, good! You're home!
哇太棒了  你在家
Hi!
嗨
Mom, I told you to text or call.
f了要ll短信或者打啊
You told me to give you a few weeks to settle in.
你告V我o你字馨差D一下
Well, it's been a few weeks, and I want to meet my new grandkids.
F在已^了字芰  而且我想看看我的O子O女
You must be Lizzy. Come here!
你肯定是吧  ^
No, she doesn't like it when you... Come here!
不  她不喜g  磉@
Oh! I'm your Grandma Sandy.
喔  我是你的奶奶珊迪
Anyone ever starts shit with any of you, they have to deal with me.
任何人想欺你  他都要先^我@P
We're family now, and I got your back forever. You hear me?
我F在是一家人了  我永h是你的后盾  你到了
Mom, just take it easy. Please. Oh, my God!
eo  拜托  哦  我的天
Will you look at them!
我能看看他
Juan, Lita, this is Sandy. This is Pete's mom.
阮  塔  @是珊迪  @是彼得的
Hi! Hi!
嗨  嗨
I could just eat you two up! And how's my baby boy?
真想把你吃了  我的大O子怎么影
Ohh!
噢
Hello, dear. Hi.
你好  H鄣  嗨
Mom, give us a few minutes. We were just in the middle of a family meeting.
o我追昼  我正在_家庭h呢
Perfect, because I'm a member of the family.
太好了  我也是@家庭的一T了
Grandma Sandy has an announcement to make.
珊迪奶奶有一件事要宣布
I got the whole family tickets to Six Flags!
我o全家人都I了去六面旗主}公@的票
Yay! Yay!
耶  耶
What's Six Flags?
六面旗是什么
"What's Six Flags?" Mom, that's such a nice offer.
六面旗是什么    @提h很好
But things have been a little chaotic around here, and we need things to be normal.
但@里的情r有c碗s  我得把一切都理好
I'll tell you what's not normal, is your kids not knowing what Six Flags is.
我砀嬖V你什么]有理好  你的孩子不知道什么是六面旗
Your kids.
你的孩子
Ma, it's just not a good time. So we're not doing this, okay?
F在不是r候  我]有在f@件事  好
We're not doing this, right? We're on the same page because of the structure thing?
我]有在f@件事    我在管理上_成共R了
Yeah, yeah.
好吧  好吧
Honey? Right, El?
H鄣  是  艾莉
I did not cave. Oh, you caved.
我才]屈服  哦  你屈服了
Lizzy gave you the look and you caved.
看了你一眼  你就屈服了
Maybe I just wanted to be the fun parent for once instead of being the bad guy.
也S我只想做孩子_心的父母而不是喝
I tried being the bad guy. You wouldn't let me. Okay, fine. I'm sorry.
我在著做娜  你不我做  好吧  是的  我很抱歉
But look how much fun everybody's having.
但每人看起矶己荛_心啊
And Lizzy, she's actually smiling. It's crazy.
她真的在笑  @太狂了
Hey! Did you have fun?
嘿  你玩得_心
You don't have to go on the kiddie rides.
你不必去玩和玩的那些目
I love the big rides. You want to go on the...
我喜g刺激的  你想去
Hey, Lizzy! Hey, what's up?
嘿    嘿  怎么了
Good to see you! Good to see you too!
很高d到你  很高d到你
Hey, hey. What's up?
嘿  嘿  怎么了
Uh, Kylie, Savanna, these are my, um...
呃  P莉  莎凡娜  他是我的  嗯
fosters.
B父母
Yeah, yeah. We're the fosters!
是的  是的  我是她的B父母
I'll see you guys later. Actually, we were just gonna go on the water ride.
待  H上  我正要去水上@呢
Let her go with her friends.
她和朋友一起去吧
They don't want to be stuck here with a bunch of old farts like you two.
她可不想和你老家伙混呆在一起
They want to ride the big stuff and check out the hot boys.
她想Tc刺激的|西  看看哥什么的
Here's a hundred.
@是一百元
Buy yourselves some souvenirs and junk food.
o自己I些o念品和好吃的
Uh-huh. Thanks, Grandma Sandy. Thanks!
嗯嗯  xx  珊迪奶奶  xx
All right, cool.
好吧  酷
Uh, meet you guys at... What time are we going back to your house?
呃  什么r候回你家
We're going back to our house, where we all live, at 7:00!
我回自己的家  我都住在那里  七c
Okay, I'll see you then. Bye!
好的  到r候  再
Mom, what are you doing? You can't... Oh, no!
你在干什么  你不能  哦  不
Little Juanny's upchucking in the trash bin!
小阮被垃圾桶卡住了
You all right, peanut?
你]事吧
Was it all the funnel cakes we ate?
把才吃的漏斗蛋糕都吐了
Oh. Oh, oh.
哦  哦  哦
I know she's getting these texts. I can see the dots.
我知道她收到了@些短信  我能看到@些c
Maybe she ran off. Maybe something happened to her.
也S她跑掉了  也S她出了什么事
No, she didn't. She's just treating us like another set of fosters.
不  她]有  她只是把我又作一B父母了
All right, bye.
好啦  再
Thanks for the ride. I love you!
xx你送我回  我勰
I'm the bad guy. Watch this. Bye.
我要娜肆  注意c  再
Bye! Hey!
再  嘿
Where the hell were you? We went to the movies.
你到底去在哪毫  我去看影了
And it ran a little bit later. It's not a big deal.
rgL了c  ]什么大不了的
You couldn't have taken five seconds to let us know nobody murdered you?
你就不能花五秒碜我知道你]有被人\
Well, guess what? You're grounded.
好吧  你猜怎么著   你被禁足了
I'm grounded? Yeah. You're grounded. Because I just grounded you.
我被禁足了  是的  你被禁足了  因槲把你禁足了
Before you weren't grounded, you weren't anything,
在你]有被禁足之前  你]事
and then I just said that thing that I said, and now you're grounded!
然后我f了我才f的  F在你被禁足了
We've been waiting one hour for you! I'm the bad guy. Calm down.
我已等了你一小r了  我懋娜  冷o
He's the bad guy. You're not going anywhere.
他懋娜  你哪阂膊荒苋チ
You're done! Done!
你完了  完了
Don't want to hear it! You know what?
不想  你知道
When I was nine I lived in a crack house.
我九q的r候住在一破房子里
So I'm pretty sure the multiplex is a comparatively safe environment.
所以我非常肯定影院是安全的h境
Oh, no. No. You don't play that trouble pass card with us.
哦  不  不  就因槟阌羞^麻┎淮表@次就]事了
Your butt's in a sling, missy!
你完蛋了  小姑娘
Oh, Grandma Sandy, I forgot. What?
哦  珊迪奶奶  我忘了  什么
I got you, um...
我o你Я  嗯
Oh, sweet Jesus.
哦  天
Will you look at this? I'm gonna wear it every day.
看看@  我每天都要穿著它
Oh, come here.
哦  ^
You know, this reminds me
你知道  @提醒了我
of when Pete and his degenerate friends stole a pizza truck.
彼得和他那些狐朋狗友偷^一v披_卡
She's good. She's good. Oh, God.
她很好  她很好  哦  天哪
Are you two gonna stand there all night,
你z要整晚都站在那
or are we gonna try to get these kids to bed at a decent hour?
是我要孩子按r睡X呢
You remember I told you we weren't special enough for this?
你得我告V^你我做的hh不
We were doing fine. You said that we were in a rut.
我做得很好  你f我是墨守成的
Maybe we were spoiled and didn't appreciate the rut.
也S我被牧  不喜g一成不的生活
The rut was easy and quiet. You know, I miss the rut. But you had to be a mommy.
那N生活味安o  你知道  我有c涯盍  但你非要
Whose idea was it to go and talk to the teenagers?
去和青少年是l的主意
We could've had a toddler who doesn't have opinions and thong underwear.
我不能找不l表意不穿丁字的小孩吧
What? You pushed us into some next-level shit!
什么  你把我推M了下一哟蔚子里
Look, we can't start turning on each other here.
著  我不能在@里互相挑
If we just stay calm and we work together,
如果我保持冷o一起鸲
we can find a way to get these little assholes out of our house!
我可以找到k法把@些小混蛋s出我的房子
Now we're talking!
F在我正在f啊
That's exactly what I was thinking. Hello!
我就是@么想的  你好
I hate them so much. Me too. They're the worst.
我非常他  我也是  他最牧
They're so ungrateful. We're doing everything for them.
他太忘恩x了  我樗做了一切
And they could give two shits. Right?
他s他什么都不能o我  是吧
But guess what? They're not adopted yet.
但你猜怎么著  他]有被正式收B
No. No, they're not.
不  不  他]有
We could just...
我可以
put 'em back.
把他就送回去
I mean, yes, we would look like the worst people in the world, but...
我是f  是的  我看起硐袷澜缟献畈畹娜  但是
Yeah, we would. And right now everybody thinks we're saints.
是的  我的  F在每人都J槲是圣人
I know. I love that part. I do love that part. That's the only good part.
我知道  我喜g@一c  我真的很喜g@一c  @是唯一的c了
Just an idea.
我有主意
What if we say that some relatives came forward?
如果我f有H戚砹四
The courts took 'em. There's nothing we could do.
法庭把他ё吡  我o能榱
Right? We squirt a few tears, we act super devastated.
Π  我再D椎窝I  表F得非常y^
That's good. That's good. That's very good.
那很好  那很好  那非常好
And we get our clean house and date night back.
然后我就有了干舻姆孔雍图s之夜
And everybody feels sorry for us.
每人都槲感到y^
Yes! Right?
是啊  Π
Get some presents maybe.
也S收些Y物
We're never gonna do that.
我永h不@么做的
No.
不
It's a nice thought, but we're...
@是好主意  但我
We're stuck, aren't we? Yeah, we are.
我被困住了  不是  是的  我被困住了
You know, we gotta just accept that we made a terrible mistake
你知道  我必承J我犯了一乐氐腻e`
and our life is mostly gonna suck now.
我的生活F在大部分都很糟糕
Good night, honey.
晚安  H鄣
All right, one nail on each side of the slat.
好了  板l蛇各有一子
Okay. On both ends. Okay?
好的  在啥硕加  可以
"Look." Yes, excellent.
看  是的  很好
Okay, keep going. Get the words for me.
好的  ^m  把@些拼出
What are you doing? You want to get in? You wanna say hi to Lizzy?
你在做什么  你想M  你想和打招呼
Speak of the devil.
f曹操曹操到
What are they doing here?
他在@里干什么
You never said I couldn't have any people over.
你]f^我不能任何人硗
Everybody knows you can't have people over when you're grounded.
每人都知道被禁足的r候是不能有人^淼
You know that too, because they obviously came in through the window.
你也知道  因樗@然是拇暨M淼
This place is disgusting, by the way.
便f一下  @地方太盒牧
God, what a Nazi bitch. What did you call me?
天  真是{粹婊子  你才f我什么
I don't know. You just seem like a Nazi bitch.
我不知道  你就像{粹婊子
Get out. Now.
出去  F在
Out. Both of you, out. Go! Now! No, you get out of my room.
出去  你  出去  去吧  F在  不  你L出我的房g
No, no, I'm staying in your black room. These guys are leaving.
不  不  我要你在@黑屋子里待著  @些人要走了
No, out the window, Pussy Riot! Way you came in!
不  拇舫鋈  造反者  哪里淼哪睦锶
Out, now! Holy shit!
出去  F在  P槽
Out! Out!
出去  出去
Oh! You're literally crazy!
哦  你真是了
You're driving me crazy! Oh, my God. What are you doing?
是你把我逼的  哦  我的天  你在做什么
You're acting like you're a psychopath. Start the car.
你看起硐精神病患者  l悠
What is going on in there? Lizzy, please, I said you're grounded.
里面l生了什么    拜托  我f你被禁足了
Where are you going? I'm calling my caseworker.
你要去哪里  我要打o我的社工
That's a good idea, huh?
好主意  嗯
Get CPS to come, make your little brother and sister pack up their court bears
警察  你的弟弟和妹妹打包他的小熊
and trash bags in the middle of the night and move them back to the Muskies?
和垃圾袋然后搬回莫斯科
That'll be really good for them. Better than you.
那λ真好  那也比你好
No! Not better than me! I can't with you. Can you please deal with her, Pete?
不  不比我好  我受不了你了  你能理一下  彼得
Hey, Lizzy, you're gonna... We're really good people!
嘿    你要  我真是好人
We just want to make a nice home for you. Is that so wrong?
我只想o你一完美的家  @硬
You're just another white lady who wants to adopt little charity orphans
你只是一想做慈善收B孤旱陌兹伺士
to make you feel good about yourself.
@能你ψ约焊杏X良好
Pete, you tell her what my nationality is! Tell her!
彼得  你告V她我是什么人  告V她
Well, actually by blood she is...
嗯  事上  她是
I'm one-eighth Comanche, okay? So I'm not that white!
我有八分之一的科曼奇族血y  好  所以我不是白人
And do I look like I feel good about myself right now?
我F在看起碛凶晕腋杏X很好
Okay, then tell me! Please tell me!
好吧  那告V我  告V我
Why did you suddenly feel the urge to get foster kids?
你槭裁赐蝗挥辛讼胍收B孩子的_
Because we... It was... I mean, I...
因槲  是  我是f  我
"Pete, please?" Exactly. No, I...
彼得  求你了  就是@  不  我
Hey, you're not going anywhere. Stop right there!
嘿  你哪憾疾荒苋  站住
I mean it. Don't open that door.
我是J真的  e打_那扇T
Hey! Do not get in that car. You hear me?
嘿  e上那v  你了
Don't shut that door. I mean it!
eP那扇T  我是J真的
Good. Now can we just go inside so we can talk about this?
很好  F在我能M去@
Juan, drop it right now!
阮  R上放下
What are you doing? Take it out!
你在做什么  把它拿出
No, better to leave it in till we get to the hospital. You're okay, buddy. We're here.
-不  最好在到t院之前e铀  你]事的  伙  我在呢
We're here. You're okay.
我在@里  你]事的
Stay still. I got to wrap it up.
猿忠幌  我得把它包起
Relax. We'll get you there in one second, okay? You're...
放p松  我R上送你去t院  好  你是
Oh, honey, Juan is gonna be okay. Come on.
哦  H鄣  阮]事的  戆
You know what? Tell the girls we need their car. Now!
你知道  告V女孩我需要他的  F在
Get out! Move your ass! Come on!
出  快c  悠  快c
I got you, buddy. I got you. Get in, get in, get in.
我在呢  孩子  我在呢  -上  上  上
Seat belts on, everybody! Seat belts on.
大家系好安全  系好安全
You're a brave boy, you hear me? Look at me. You're so brave. Yeah?
你是勇敢的孩子  到了  看著我  你真勇敢  Π
You're doing such a good job, buddy. We're right here.
你做的太棒了  伙  我就在@里呢
Hello! Hey, help, please.
你好  嘿  救救他
What happened? He's got a nail in his foot.
l生什么事了  他_上有根子
I didn't want to take it out, just in case.
我不想拿出硪苑廊f一
That was very smart. Put him right on this gurney.
那很明  把他放在@床上
Hey, buddy. It's all right, buddy. We're here.
嘿  伙  ]事的  伙  我在@呢
Are you the mother? Yes. Oh, I'm his foster mom.
你是母H  是的  哦  我是他的B母
Okay. Right this way, Dad.
好的  @走  爸爸
Hey, buddy, what's your name?
嘿  伙  你叫什么名字
Juan, we're gonna clean this off, give you a little anesthetic,
阮  我要把@清理干  o你打一麻醉
and then take this nail out.
然后把子拿出
Hold my hand. Gonna be a little pinch. Look at me.
握住我的手  可能有c疼  看著我
Hold my hand, hold my hand. A little bit of a sting.
抓住我的手  抓住我的手  有c刺痛
Stop! Stop! It's almost over.
停下  住手  快好了
That's it. It's done! It's done. It's done.
就是@  好了  好了  好了
I think we should take Lita to the lobby.
我想我塔去大d
You want to go with her or stay here with Juan?
你想和她一起去是留下砼闳钅
You take her.
你抱著她吧
Come here. Hey, I'm right here.
^  嘿  我就在@
He's okay. You're so brave.
]事了  你真勇敢
You're doing so good, buddy.
你做得太好了  伙
So he doesn't have to wear a cast or anything? It's just stitches?
所以他不必穿石膏什么的  只是p
Yeah. Well, that's good news.
是的  好吧  @是好消息
And how did this happen?
@是怎么l生的呢
It was my fault. I walked away, and I left the gun there.
@是我的e  我走_了  把留在了那里
Juan just picked it up. No. It wasn't their fault. It was mine.
阮把它炝似  不  不是他的e  是我的e
I was trying to leave in a car and I wasn't supposed to,
我想_x_  但我不x_
and then they got distracted, and then I yelled at Juan,
然后他分心了  然后我θ畲蠛按蠼
and he dropped the thing on his foot...
然后他手上的掉到了_上
Don't be ridiculous. I should never have left the nail gun there.
e扯淡了  我不把留在那
Pete, shut up! This is the kind of stuff they move kids for, okay?
彼得  ]嘴  @就是他孩子搬走的原因  好
It wasn't their fault. They didn't do anything.
@不是他的e  他什么都]做
I should be the one getting in trouble right now. It's okay.
我是犯了e的人  ]P系
Why don't you come on over here? Excuse me.
你槭裁床贿^磉@里呢  抱歉
And, uh, let's talk about what happened.
我碚l生了什么
So, uh, nobody's being moved.
所以  呃  ]有人被搬走
Hey. What's wrong?
嘿  怎么了
Uh, I have no idea. I just woke up this morning and...
呃  我不知道  今天早上我醒
Damn it.
死的
You know what? I think I can help.
你知道  我想我能兔
I have a...
我有一
I have this really great detangler. You want me to...?
我有一很棒的梳子  要不要我
Sure, yeah. Yeah, whatever, yeah. Yeah?
然  是的  是的  管他呢  然了  是
Okay, here.
好吧  @里
Have a seat, and I'll... Yeah.
坐下  我  是啊
Okay.
好的
Wow. How'd this happen? I don't know.
哇  怎么@  我不知道
Yeah. Just let me know if it pulls, okay?
是啊  如果拽到^l了就跟我f  好
Okay. That's good.
好的  搞定了
Better, yeah? Oh, wow. Yeah. Thank you.
好多了  是吧  哦  哇  是啊  xx了
Let me just smooth it out for you.
我再把它弄c
Thank you.
xx了
No problem. It's all gone.
]P系  一切都^去了
You all set? Yep.
都浜昧  浜昧
Hey, thanks for the lunch. No problem.
嘿  xx你的午餐  ]P系
Oh, is that that boy Jacob?
哦  那是雅各布
The one that just picked up that bit of trash?
炝死圾的那
Don't freak out about it. No! Why would I freak out about it?
e大@小怪  ]有  我槭裁匆大@小怪呢
He looks like an artistic type, like you said.
就像你f的  他看起硐褚g型的人
You think so? Definitely!
你真的@么J  然了
Look at that face. Yeah.
看看那  是啊
Conscientious. Picking up trash.
挺有任心的  知道把垃圾炱
Yeah. Yeah, he is. Yeah.
是啊  是  他是
Well, have a good day. Thanks. You too.
好的  祝你有愉快的一天  xx  你也是
Okay. All right.
好的  好的
Careful with your foot, Juan. Bye, Lita.
小心你的_  阮  再  塔
Well, did you see that?
你看到了
Definitely starting to hate me a bit less, right?
肯定_始不那么恨我了  Π
Maybe.
也S吧
Hi, Lizzy. Hey, Charlie.
嗨    嘿  查利
Hi, Jacob.
嗨  雅各布
Wassup, baby girl? Nothing.
怎么了 小  ]什么
How you doing? I'm good. Cleaning up your mess.
你怎么  我挺好  收拾你的子
Why don't you get into school before you get me in trouble.
你槭裁床辉诮o我惹麻┲前早cMW校呢
All right, fine.
好的  ]}
Text me. Okay.
系我  -]}
Hey, hon. Hey.
嗨  H鄣  嗨
Hi. How's she doing? She's good.
她做得怎么  她挺好的
Oh. Yeah. And check this out.
噢α  有事
I got here early, Lizzy saw me, and she came over and just starts
我今天到早了  看到我  然后就
talking.
_始f了
To you? Yeah!
跟你f  Π
Not, like, full-on girl talk, but not the usual silent treatment either.
不是那N乖女孩的聊天  也不是平常的冷
She was telling me about that kid Jacob,
她居然跟我v了那叫雅各布的男孩
and how he doesn't say much so she can't tell if he likes her.
有他不怎么f  她不知道他是不是喜g她
Next thing I know I'm in full mom mode, giving her advice, like,
下一刻我就M入了模式  o她建h  比如
"Well, sometimes with the quiet types you'll have to make the first move."
害羞的男孩有r候你要~出第一步
You said "make a move"? You told her to make a move on a boy?
你f什么第一步  你她δ泻⑦~出第一步
This kid is harmless, baby. Trust me.
@是好男孩    相信我
I'm thrilled she even likes him. I totally pegged her for the bad boys.
]想到她居然喜g他  我想她凵弦哪泻
What happened? Juan broke Potato Chips.
怎么回事啦  阮弄牧耸l
Calm down. I'm gonna fix her, okay? Here you go. See?
e哭e哭  我可以修好她的  看  修好啦
Thanks, Daddy.
xx  耙耙
Did you hear that? I just got my first "Daddy"!
你有到  她叫我爸爸
That's... You suck!
你作弊了吧
No fair! I want some of that. Hey, honey.
不公平  我也要  嗨  H鄣
Lita, can I help you with anything? Nope!
塔  我有什么可以偷侥  ]有
No, what? Are you talking to me? Who am I?
什么]有  你是跟我f  我是l啊
Ellie. Juan. Buddy, come here!
艾莉  阮    磉@
Come here, Son.
磉@  乖鹤
How's your foot? You okay? You okay if I call you "Son"?
你的|西好吃  我叫你鹤幽憧梢越邮馨
Sure.
然啦
Where's Lizzy? Right there. See her?
去哪毫  就在那  看得到
Oh, yeah, she's right there.
噢然  她就在那
She just comes out here, she takes all this stuff out,
她磉@  然后翻了底朝天
and she can't bother with the one second it takes
她甚至不用一秒
to close a stupid door or put anything in the sink.
P上@T或者放K|西到水槽里
What happened? I found my hairbrush in the toilet this morning.
l生了什么  我早上在R桶里找到我的梳子
What? I told you that wasn't me!
什么鬼  我都f了不是我放的
Of course it was you. I left it in the bathroom for you.
不是你是l  是我留在浴室o你用的
Juan and Lita aren't even up yet. I'm up now, Miss Noisy Pants.
阮和塔都]起床  我起床啦  吵[小姐
I'm sorry, sweetie. I thought we were really connecting.
Σ黄鸢∥业男  我以槲P系在好
I left it there for her with a nice little note, with hearts on it and stuff.
我留在那o她用N了坌男”阗N
Oh, my God. I didn't do it.
我滴天哪  不是我扔MR桶的
Wow. Hello. What is that?
哇哦  你好  @是什么鬼
You're wearing that? Are you going to a strip club?
你穿著@衣服是去衣舞俱凡
Sorry I don't dress like an uptight douche like you.
Σ黄  我不像你穿得像焦]的沙雕那
You don't talk to my wife like that! This is from Ann Taylor. Loft!
你不能@雍臀依掀耪f  @是安泰勒w堑囊路O
You know what? Go put some clothes on, a lot of them.
so去穿外套  越多越好
Then get in my truck. I'm driving you this morning. Oh, my God!
然后上  今天早上我送你  我滴天哪
You guys are so annoying!
你真的很吵O
Change the clothes. It's not that big of a deal.
去Q衣服  @又不是什么大事
Hey. Do I dress like a douche?
嗨  我穿得像沙雕
No. Make sure she gets out to my truck. Bye, Daddy.
]有  看著她她上我的  再啦  耙耙
Bye, sweetie.
再  小
Oh, my goodness. Oh.
死我了
Hey, what's that? Oh!
怎么回事喊
You okay?
你]事吧
That's a shame.
真的太羞u了
What are we doing here? Let's go.
我在干嘛呢  走啦
I'm gonna be late for school, you know.
我t到的  你知道
Come on.
M戆
Okay. So you're punishing me with manual labor.
哦嚯  所以你F在是wP我咯
I've worked harder than you've ever...
我任何r候都比你更努力地活著
Yeah, I know, you're a badass.
嗯我知道  你很了不起
This isn't a punishment, okay? Hey!
@不是土P  好吧  嗨
I'm Stewart. You probably... You... What's up?
我是Stewart  你就是  你好
Stewart. Don't ever talk to her again, okay?
斯D特e再跟她f好
As a matter of fact, go to lunch. It's 8:15.
有  你去吃午餐  @才八c十五分O
Okay. Lunch it is.
好吧  午餐rg
Come on.
^
Put these on. What?
把@些穿上  什么鬼
Just put them on.
eU  穿上
Lizzy, I know you're angry.
我知道你很生
At us, at the world. Maybe at yourself a little bit.
不爽我  不爽@世界  可能也有c不爽你自己
I don't know, and you're not talking.
我不知道  你又不肯f
Truth is, when I'm pissed, I don't like to talk about it either.
事是  我生獾r候也不想f
But you know what I do like to do?
但你知道我生做什么
Oh! I like to break shit.
啊  我生r喜g搞破
R... Really?
真的
Anything in this room.
@屋子里的任何|西
Swing away. Okay.
砸起  嗯嗯
Huh? How'd that feel? It felt good!
怎么  感X爽  爽啊
Feels good, huh? I told you. Yeah.
]_你吧  嗯嗯
Now... Whoa, whoa! Don't waste it, all right? I want you to do me a favor.
停停停  e浪M  F在我想你臀忙
I need you to think about something that really pisses you off.
我需要你想些真的能搞毛你的事
You got it? I got it.
明白]  明白了
Let's see it. Bust that shit up.
好的呢  砸它
Yes!
爽
There you go. You like that? Yeah, that was good.
爽吧 你喜g不  然  非常爽
All right, come on.
好  接著
There we go. Yes!
爽吧
Ho-ho! Double shot!
哈哈p
You like that?
爽完了吧
That was cool.
超爽的
So no school today, huh?
所以今天不上W了
Pete took me to the house you're flipping. Hmm.
皮特我去你正在b修的屋子了  嗯哼
We did some demo work. That's cool.
我做了些了不得的工作  嗯  挺好的
Um, hey, hey, come on.
嗨嗨嗨  ^
About that hairbrush?
那R桶里的梳子
my mom used to brush my hair...
我H以前是臀沂犷^的
and I don't know, I'm sorry.
我不知道  很Σ黄
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
]P系的  我也有e
No, you have no reason to be sorry. No, I'm really sorry.
不不  你]有e  才不是呢  真的Σ黄
All right.
好
I'm gonna go clean up. Hairbrush is in the toilet, if you need it.
我F在去收拾干  如果你需要的梳子在R桶里
Good one.
干得漂亮
Thank you.
xx
You wanna rotate like this, okay?
你要@愚D痈觳膊判
Yeah.
就是@
Juan hit me!
阮打我了
Oh, no. Oh, God!
啊 我的天哪
Hey, number three, where's your mother?
嘿  三球T  把你叫^
I'm okay. Okay.
我]事  ]事就好
I didn't hit her!
我]有打她
Juan, where did you put my phone?
阮你把我手C藏哪毫
I didn't take your phone! No, I didn't!
我]有拿你的手C  我真的]有
All right! First try!
好  第一次L
There you go. Dad, Dad, Dad!
W了]  爸 爸 爸
There you go, Juan.
拿好了阮
Spit it out, spit it out!
吐出  吐出
Here, water! No, we need ice!
接住  水  不  我需要冰
Water, water. Here. Oh, gosh.
水砹 水砹  天哪
Hey.
嘿
Hey, buddy.
嘿  小
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey. It's okay, sweetie. Did you have a bad dream?
嘿  一切安好呢小  你l噩袅
Yeah. Yeah?
嗯嗯  真的啊
You're okay. You're safe and sound in your bed.
]有事的  你在被C里很安全
You're good.
你四肢健在呢
Good night, buddy.
晚安啦  小
Good night, Mommy.
晚安  嘛嘛
What?
什么
What did you say?
你f什么了
Juan, what did you say?
阮  能在f一次
Did you say something, Juan?
你是不是叫我了  阮
Hey, Juan, what did you say?
嘿  阮  你是叫我了吧
Juan!
阮
Juan! Did you say something? Juan!
阮  再叫我一次吧  阮
Juan, what did you say?
阮  就再f一次嘛
Juan!
阮
Oh, my God.
我的天哪
Good night, buddy.
晚安啦  小
Hey. Hey!
嘿  嘿
Wow, it's looking good. Huh? You like it?
哇哦  @看起砗芡昝勒O   嗯哼  你喜g
Check it out. I put the storage at the end of the island, like you suggested.
看看那  我按照你意思把Σ毓癜丛诹N房u的M^
Oh, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
哇  @真的太棒了
Great idea, by the way. It's awesome.
便一提  那真是好主意  太炫酷了吧
Why don't you come help us hang some tile? Yeah.
^臀N一些瓦吧  Π
No, I, uh...
不了  我
So, there's, um...
那么  @里有
There's something I'd like to do,
有些事情我想去做
and I was hoping I could get your help setting it up.
我想您臀湟幌
Sure. What are we setting up? Of course. Anything.
]}  我要湫┦裁  什么都行
So I was talking to Karen and Sharon, and they...
我跟P和莎^
Uh, my mom got out a few months ago, so...
我月前走了
And I haven't seen her. I was hoping I could see her.
我最近都]^她  我想和她面
Yeah, sure. Yeah, of course.
可以  ]}  然可以
Of course. I mean, that's... Yeah.
肯定可以的啊  嗯嗯
Cool. Thanks.
好的  xx您
Yeah. It's cool. Great.
]什么  嗯  }不大
Okay. Thanks.
太xx了
You, uh...
您  ~
I'll just wait outside. Okay.
那我就在外面等吧
Hi.
嗨
Juan, Lita.
阮  塔
Hey, Juan, Lita, come on!
嘿  阮  塔  快^
Come on.
快砜
What's wrong? Come on. I want to stay with Mom.
怎么回事了呢  我想和嘛嘛呆著
Your mommy's over there.
你的在那里啊
It's okay, sweetheart. It's okay, honey.
]P系的  小  嗯嗯  ]P系的  H鄣
We're gonna go with you. We're right here.
我和你一起^去  我就在@里
We'll walk together. Come on.
我一起走吧  快砜
Slow down.
慢c郝
Oh, my babies, you got so big!
噢  我的孩子  你已@么大了啊
Come, mi amor.
斫o我抱抱
Hi, I'm Sue. I'm Carla's caseworker.
嗨  我是休  我是卡拉的社工
You must be Pete and Ellie? Yeah, I'm Pete. Hi.
你肯定就是皮特和艾莉了  嗯嗯  我是Pete  嗨
Hey. I'm Ellie.
嗨  我是艾莉
This is Carla. She's... Their mom.
@是卡拉  她是  孩子的H
Hi. I'm Ellie. Nice to meet you.
嗨  我是艾莉  非常高d到你
I'm Pete.
我是皮特
Hey, I wanted to say thank you for watching them while I was...
嘿  我想fxx你兔φ疹他在
No problem. They've been doing great.
]P系  他都很乖
Juan started playing piano. Right, buddy?
阮_始W琴了Π  小家伙
And Lita just got 100 on her last spelling test.
塔在拼y拿了一百分
And Lizzy's soccer team is undefeated.
的足球打遍天下o呈
All right, so you guys gonna pick us up at 4:00?
好的  那么你四c斫踊匚吧
Okay. We'll see you in a bit.
]}  待
Yeah, we'll be back. We'll be back soon.
嗯嗯  我很快就回  很快就回
Bye, guys. Nice to meet you.
再啦  小家伙  很高d到你
You okay?
你行
"Thanks for watching them"? Like we've just been fricking babysitting for five months?
xx你照他  我就像做了五月保姆
She's just not what I pictured at all.
她根本不像我以榈哪
She's... She kind of looks normal.
她  她看起砗苷常
I feel bad, like we're breaking up a family.
我感X不太好  就像我在破e人的家庭
We didn't take her kids, Ellie.
我]有走她的孩子  艾莉
The courts did. And don't forget why.
是法庭了  有e忘了起因
Those kids were living like feral cats in a crack house.
@些孩子之前生活得就像破屋里的野
I know, I know, but she kind of... She looks okay.
我知道  我知道  但她看起磉是很正常的
I mean, Sharon said she's been clean for four months.
我的意思是  莎f她已四月]犯事了
Yeah, she got clean because she was in jail, Ellie.
嗯  她]犯事  那是因樗坐^牢了啊  艾莉
Look at the way Lizzy's looking at her.
看看看著她H的眼神
She's still her mom.
她H是她H
We didn't take her kids, Ellie.
我]有走她的孩子啊  艾莉
So I said, "Young lady,
那r我就f  @位年p女士
we hear about you throwing food in the cafeteria one more time,
如果我再一次f你在咖啡d里y扔食物
and you're gonna have a couple of lunch dates."
你就多次和我一起吃午餐
Next day, the behavior continued.
第二天  她是y扔食物
So we went to the school and joined her in the cafeteria.
所以我去了她的W校然后和她一起吃午
Chattin' up all her middle school BFFs.
和她所有的中W好朋友聊了天
I walked them through some of my better bird-watching stories.
我跟他v了一些我最好的的^B故事
They were completely uninterested.
但他完全不感d趣
But that food throwing has stopped!
不^她就]有再y扔食物了
Good. Good.
妙啊  妙啊
Would you like to share your news?
你愿意分享一下你的故事
About the couch fire? No. About your .26 hearing.
P于沙l著火的故事  不  P于你的二六
Yes.
嗯嗯
The court has legally cleared us...
法庭已依照法律
to adopt.
把孩子判o我了
To adopt Tina and Ryan!
把娜和瑞安判o我了
Yay! That is so great.
太好啦  @真的太棒了
Congratulations, guys. I'm so happy for you.
恭喜啊  我非常槟感到高d
That is such great news. I'm so happy for both of you.
@真是非常好的一消息  我槟感到高d
And next we have Pete and Ellie.
那么下面有皮特和艾莉
Well, you know, our kids have, what,
好吧  你知道  我的孩子已
had now four visits with their birth mom?
回去了他H四次了
Yeah. And every time they do,
嗯哼  每一次他都非常
they're just crazy for a few days after.
非常d^  特e在了他H后的那滋
Holy...
天哪
And just when things finally start to feel normal again,
他平o下砗  一切如常的r候
they have another visit.
他就再去他H
Yeah, we just feel so rejected.
嗯嗯  我感X被排D得很乐
And I know this probably makes me a really bad person,
我也知道@可能你X得我很
but I just keep wishing that their mom would go back to prison.
但我真的一直希望他H能回去坐牢
You're not a bad person.
你才不是娜四
When someone does terrible things to the children we love,
有人ξ心鄣暮⒆幼龀隹膳碌氖虑槭
it's not easy to find empathy for them.
我很yδ人a生同情
But we have to try, people.
但我是要M量去著同情
Whatever happens, the time that your kids spent with you
ol生什么  孩子陪伴你的rg
made a big difference in their lives. Mm-hmm.
已λ人生a生很大影  嗯哼
Yeah, I know, but then we're just supposed to...
嗯  我知道  但我就理去
Wait. Did you say "made" a difference? Yeah, she did.
等等  你f已λa生影  Φ
We-We'll talk after.
我之后再
No. She said "made." That's past tense. There's a difference.
不 她f已  @是^去式  @就是不同
I wanna know what's going on, Karen.
我想知道@是什么r  P
Well...
好吧
Since Lizzy's mom has been keeping up with her reunification steps,
b于的H已逐步_始c她的孩子重w于好
the judge changed your .26 hearing to a Change of Circumstances hearing
法官把孩子判o你的事可能伊
where he'll decide if the kids are ready to reunite.
法官Q定孩子是否跟回他H生活
Nice.
棒
Really nice.
太棒了
No, this is...
@直就是
You weren't gonna share that with us?
你打算[m著我
We've been dealing with all of this shit!
我一直在和@破事杭mp
I mean, the tantrums, the messes, the attitude.
我是f  他yl脾  弄得家里一F糟  有那可怕的B度
I have played 150 games of Candy Land with Lita.
我甚至已和塔玩了一百五十次糖果@
You ever play fricking Candy Land?
你玩^糖果世界
It's brutal! It's very dull.
太痛苦了  o聊透了
We're making connections. Okay?
我著和她多交流
I mean I just taught Lita how to ride a bike.
所以打算教塔WT自行
Juan and I bonded over Rocky III.
阮和我在看《洛基 III》
And now Mom's ready to reunite?
F在就B也要胶瓦M砹
Pete, Ellie, I understand your frustration.
彼得  艾莉  我知道你很失望
But we all need to keep in mind that until the kids are adopted,
但要知道我C的首要目司褪
the primary goal of the system is family preservation.
孩子受到家庭的庇o
And what about preserving our family? Yeah.
那又有l肀Ｗo我的家庭呢  l砟
Nothing has been decided yet.
事情]有w棺定
All right, October, that leaves you.
那好  接下  W克托布
Well, I have gotten a placement.
嗯 我也收B了一大孩子
Oh. He is 14 and does play JV basketball.
他14q了  ⒓恿松倌昊@球
But he is 5'2."
他身高有c低
And white, with red hair.
皮w很白染著t^l
Absolutely no fundamentals whatsoever.
也]什么基A
Oh, I get it. My problems seem stupid now.
~  好吧  看起砦业}有c不合r宜
Why do I always have to go last?
槭裁次铱是最后一呢
Stop. Okay. I know. It's...
停下戆  -好的  我想f
It's very unprofessional.
@很不I
This is the opposite of a support group.
@直就是互助小M的反例
What am I gonna look like?
我成什么幼
You're gonna look like a beautiful princess. Oh!
你看起硐漂亮的公主哦  哇
Do I look like a flower?
那我像花朵一用利
Hey. Hey, hey, buddy.
嘿  嘿  嘿  伙
Mom. Hey, kids. Oh! Hi, honey!
-  嘿  孩子  -哦  嗨  H鄣
Hey. Mom!
嘿
No, no, no. It's totally washable.
]事的 ]事的  它可以被洗掉的
It's, um... That's a Sharpie.
可是  那是P
Oh, yeah. Oh, dear.
~  是的  ~  H鄣
Can you please get off the counter, honey? It's dangerous.
H鄣  你能墓褡由舷  @很危U
How was care group? So much fun.
互助小M怎么  太有趣了
Hey, hey, hey. We have news.
嘿  嘿  嘿  我想告V你消息
You're pregnant? Oh, my God!
-你言辛  哦  天哪
Why are you doing this to me? I'm sorry. No?
你槭裁催@么f  Σ黄  那是什么消息呢
It's okay. No. Just tell them.
快把消息告V他吧
Yeah? Uh-huh.
_定
Okay, okay.
R上  R上
We are going to adopt through foster care, just like you guys!
我也打算通^寄B所眍IB孩子
I mean, we did not get it at first,
m然我不能言
and then we met yours and saw what a wonderful choice it was.
但是我遇到了你  看到了收B孩子@N方式
Hell of a lot cheaper than in vitro too.
比做管阂便宜的多了
Which is not the reason, but it's a reason, if you're weighing factors.
在@Q定中 你ξ的影挺大的
And we start classes next week!
所以我打算下周_始上n啦
What do you guys think?
你X得怎么
I think, uh...
我想  呃
I think I have to take a crap.
真是令人作I
That's not the reaction we were looking for on that.
@好像不是我期待中的反
She's jealous!
她一定是在嫉妒
Oh! Hey! Oh, my God! What are you doing?
哦  嘿  哦  天哪  你在做什么
What's going on? Please give this to me. Lizzy!
怎么了  把@o我  Lizzy
You're not allowed to take my phone! What's she doing?
你不能拿走我的手C  她在做什么
God! She's taking naked selfies in the bathroom!
天哪  她在浴室里拍裸照
She's taking naked selfies of herself? What are you doing to my phone?
她在拍自己的裸照  e游业氖C
I'm deleting everything here! Delete, delete, delete.
我要h除里面的所有热  全部h除
How many photos did you take? What is wrong with you?
你到底拍了多少  你到底槭裁催@么做
Everyone does it! It's no big deal!
大家都@么做  ]什么大不了的
It's a big, huge, giant deal!
@很有}  @很重要
Fifteen-year-old girls should never be naked, ever!
15q的女孩要自尊自
Can you take the door? Don't read my texts! Open the door!
你能拉著T  不能看我的短信  把T打_
"If you don't show me something soon, I might lose interest."
如果你不R上o我看照片  我可就]什么d趣了
What? Who is this person, Lizzy? Open the door!
什么  @人是l    _T
Oh, no. No, no. Dick pic! There's a dick pic!
哦  不  不  不  色情照  有色情照
Come on, kids, we are going in the living room.
戆  孩子  我去客d呆著
Is this that kid Jacob you were talking about?
你是在和一叫雅各布的人聊天
That sweet kid from school is sending you photos of his beeswax?
那o你寄他性感照片的男孩
Jesus, that is a trout!
天哪  @可是老油l
Get out of here!
x_@里
Lizzy! Get out here now!
F在快出
Give me the phone! Let go!
把o我  放_
This is not cool Lizzy! I don't have to listen to you anymore,
@并不r髦    我再也不想你f了
Pretend Mom!
你@假
This isn't...
不是...
Still think it's a wonderful choice?
你猿诌@是一好的x
Our foster kids aren't gonna act like that.
我的孩子不@么做的
That's on you guys.
只是你的孩子而已
What exactly is a dick pic?
Dic pic是什么
What do you think it is, Mom? Wild guess. Dick. Pic.
你X得是什么呢    色情照啊
You know, honey, when I had... times like this,
H鄣  我…面R@N}的r候
I had to search myself
我是不嗨伎
and remember...
并回
why I became a mother in the first place.
一_始槭裁次疫x癯橐幻母H
And that was helpful.
@N思考很有椭
Is this that kid Jacob's house? Is that where we're going?
@是雅各布家  就是我要去的地方
Just calm down, okay? Please tell me where we are.
冷oc  好  告V我咱在哪里
I don't want to get arrested.
我可不想被逮捕
Will you just trust me? Come on.
你只需要相信我就行  下吧
Oh. Hi.
哦  你好
Hey. I don't know if you guys remember us.
嘿  我不知道你是否得我
Pete and Ellie from foster orientation?
寄B所^的的彼得和艾莉
Oh, yeah. Hi. How you doing?
哦  得  嗨  你好
Uh, what can we do for you?
呃  我能槟阕鲂┦裁茨
So now she wants to come back and be Mommy again.
所以F在她想回碓僖淮纬橐晃荒赣H
And it looks like she's got a real shot.
而且看起硭真的有C
Lizzy, she's treating us like we're the enemy.
她Υ我就像Υ橙艘
Now we don't know what the hell to do.
F在我不知道怎么k
So I just thought, I mean, your daughter turned out so great.
所以我想知道槭裁茨的女喝绱秀
Is she up there studying? Hey, Brenda, you gonna come down?
她在那里W  嘿  布m_  你要下
I thought maybe we could speak with her,
我想和她
and she'd get us pumped up like before.
也S能我像之前一颖в邢Ｍ
Is that a possibility? Yeah, that'd be great. She was amazing.
有可能  Φ  那太好了  她太棒了
We could use a pep talk right now.
我需要一次鼓舞人心的
Um, Brenda is, um... back in rehab.
嗯  布m_她  嗯…回到康椭行牧
Excuse me, what? We caught her using a couple months ago.
Σ黄  什么  月前我lF她在吸毒
Are you shitting me right now?
你在跟我_玩笑
Her inspirational, heartwarming goddamn speech
她那鼓舞人心  令人心缟疋的演v
is the reason we signed up for this shit-show in the first place!
是我初竺⒓踊拥闹饕原因
Now you're telling me she's back on... Ow!
F在你告V我她又回了老幼印噢
You listen to me, crazy woman!
你我f  女人
Brenda has struggled with substance abuse
布m_一直在同毒品作斗
ever since her mother's boyfriend started her on meth when she was 11.
她11q的r候被她母H的男朋友注射了冰毒
Sometimes she stumbles. But she is a good kid.
有r她走入歧途  但她是好孩子
And she's in there doing the work, getting herself clean.
她J真干活  把自己整理的干干
So you don't know what's gonna happen.
你不知道l生什么
And this has you feeling what? Frustrated? Scared? Lost? Is that it?
所以你感到沮  害怕  失落
Yes! I'm a little afraid to say anything, but yes, that's basically
我有c害怕  是的  ]e@就是
how we feel.
我的感受
That's how your children feel every day of their lives.
@也正是你孩子每天的生活感受
When you took this on, you felt good about yourself
你IB他的r候  你自我感X良好
because you knew that it mattered, right?
因槟阒道@很重要  Π
Well, guess what.
好吧  大家都知道的
Things that matter are hard.
重要的事情往往很困y
Now I know where Brenda
F在我知道布m_那
gets her inspiring speech thing.
鼓舞人心的演v是哪睦淼撵`感了
Listen, guys, right now, you're all they've got.
著  F在  你就是孩子的全部
So your job is to keep them safe,
所以你的工作就是保C他的安全
whether they want you to or not.
不他是否接受
He's got it too.
他也被移默化的影了
That was incredible. Thank you.
太不可思h了  xx您
I'm so sorry that I blew up at you.
很抱歉我δ愦蟀l脾
I'm sorry I slapped you!
扇了你一巴掌
I know! That was crazy! I know. I apologize.
]事  @很好  嗯  十分抱歉
It was good. I needed it. I haven't been slapped for a long time.
@很好  我需要它  我好久]挨耳光了
It was a bit aggressive. It was a little bit out of line.
醍醐灌  茅塞D_
Well, you were, honey. You were.
可以可以  H鄣
All right, honey, we gotta go.
好吧  H鄣  我得走了
We gotta get going. Take care.
我得走了  保重
Thank you.
xx您
You're on Facebook, right? I'll find you. Okay!
在Facebook上能找到你Π  我P注你的
Bye! Bye! Thank you!
再  再  xx您
Bye.
再
Let's get in the house right away, really quick.
我快M屋吧  快c
Okay, you're all set. Bye, Lizzy.
好的  你到啦  再
Have a great day.
^得愉快哦
All right, look, you drop them off.
接下  你把他送到W校
I'm gonna find this Jacob kid and get to the bottom of this, okay?
我找到@雅各布@小子  把事情搞清楚  好
Okay. All right.
好的  好的
Wait, Pete, that's him! What?
等等  彼得  就是他  什么
Him? That redhead kid right there? The kid with the soup can for a...?
那拿著罐子的t^l男生
Come on. I'm getting him.
戆  我要抓住他
You! Dick pic! Hey! Hey!
你  猥男  嘿  嘿
Hey! Excuse me. What's up, man? Wanted to catch a fade, huh?
嘿 有事  伙  想翁
Dick pic! Think it's okay?
猥男  bo辜
Sending pictures of your knob to a 15-year-old girl?
把你的小弟弟照片lo一15q的女孩
You're lucky I don't end your life right now, carrot top.
真幸\  我]有R上懒四  小}卜
I saw what you wrote to her: "If you don't show me something, I'm
我看到你o她的信：  如果你不睃c什么  我
gonna lose interest."
失去d趣的
That's actually sexual assault, young man. It's disgusting!
那是性侵犯  年p人  真盒
Not such a big man now, are you? Come on, whip it out!
你不是大K^    秀一下
Show everybody those big shaved plums you're so proud of!
大家看看你橹傲的大家伙
We're gonna call your mom, tell the principal, maybe even call the
我要打o你  告V校L
police.
要缶
What do you think of that, Jacob? My name's not Jacob!
你X得怎么  雅各布  我不是雅各布
What? My name is Charlie.
什么  我叫查理
That's Charlie.
他是查理
I thought you said his name was Jacob. Really?
我以槟愦_定他就是雅各布  e了
And my plums aren't shaved.
我的小弟弟]刮毛
Or big.
他不大
I'm so sorry. Oh, God. I'm so sorry, honey.
我很抱歉  哦  天哪  我很抱歉  H鄣
Come on, buddy, suck it up. It's a little snafu, okay?
戆  伙  深呼吸  @是`
Come on. Give me a hug, Charlie.
戆  o我一肀  查理
All right, look at me.
放松  看著我
Do you happen to know anybody named Jacob
你JR叫雅各布的人
who might be hanging around with our daughter, Lizzy Viara?
l和我的女蝴在一起
The janitor? The adult-ass janitor?
看T人  成人用品店的看T人
Oh, my God. Come on, let's get the janitor.
-我的天  走  我去找看T人
Hey, I'm so sorry about this. Ellie, come on!
嘿  我很抱歉  艾莉  快c
Thank you so much! He didn't do any of that.
非常感x  和他oP
Come on, Ellie. He didn't do any of it!
快c  艾莉 和他]有一cP系
Hurry up! I'm so sorry, Charlie!
快c  Σ黄  查理
I think we're gonna be late for school.
我上W要t到了
Ellie
艾莉
He's on a Zamboni. Come on!
他在吃早  加油
Hey! Hey, you!
嘿  嘿  叫你呢
Excuse me. I'm talking to you.
嘿  我在和你f呢
How old are you, Jump Street? Why you want to know?
你多大了  你想知道什么
Hey, lady, gimme that. That's not yours. He's 22!
-嘿  女士  把那我  那不是你的  他22q了
He's 22. Yeah, I'm 22. So what?
他22q  是的  我22q了  那又怎么
So this won't be child abuse. Pete!
所以我不是在虐待和  彼得
Hey, you ever touch, text, or think about our daughter ever again,
嘿  你之前碰^  想^  系^我女  要是再有下次
and you're a dead man.
那你就死定了
I'm gonna sue you, man! You're not even her parents!
我要起V你  你不是她的H生父母
Would not-her-parents do this?
她H生父母y道不@幼
Miss Peppers!
佩佩小姐
Whoa. Whoa. What's happening here?
哇  哇  l生了什么
This man has been sending lewd comments and photos to our daughter.
他一直o我女喊l送淫xu和照片
You're going to jail today, Jacob! You mind calling the police?
你今天要坐牢了  Jacob  你介意缶
Absolutely! Miss Peppers!
必缶  佩佩小姐
Mother...
…
All right. We appreciate it.
xx  我很感激
Man, I didn't even touch that girl.
伙  我都]碰^那女孩
Bye-bye, scumbag. Filthy pedophile.
L蛋吧  混蛋  盒牡偻癖
Yeah. Enjoy your life as a sex offender.
L去享受性侵犯者的生活
Pedophile.
盒牡偻癖
You're arresting us? The guy was sending pictures of his knob to a
槭裁创捕我  那家伙把他的色情照
minor.
lo了未成年
Why are you arresting us? Really good. Good work, guys.
-你槭裁匆逮捕我  非常好  干得好
For what it's worth, I heard what you guys did in there.
必要f  我f了你的光x事E
You're good parents, looking out for your kids.
你是好父母  照你的孩子
If I'd had a chance to do the same...
如果又C  我做同拥倪x瘛
The kids! Oh, my God!
孩子  哦  天哪
Juan, Lita! Oh, my God, I'm so sorry! Guys!
阮  塔  哦  天哪  真Σ黄  孩子
Hey. Hey, baby.
嘿  嘿
My God, it's so clean.
天哪  真干
Well, there are my little gangsters.
嗯  我的小“匪徒”回砹
Posting bail for my Petey.
保金交^了
Really took me back to the good old days.
我真的回到了^去的美好r光
Thank you, by the way. Where are the kids?
xx  孩子在哪里
Karen had to take them to a temporary placement for the night.
P不得不把他У揭Rr的地方^夜
She said it's the first time she's heard of CPS
她f@是她第一次fCPS在孩子C
removing kids from their adoptive home the night before their hearing.
的前一天晚上把他募酿B家庭ё
Speaking of which, I found your statement to the judge on your printer.
f到@  我看了你打印下淼年述~
Needs some work.
需要M行一些修改
Mom, it's too late. We submitted it last week.
太晚了  我上周已提交了
Well, resubmit it! Jesus!
M管如此  是要重新提交一份
"We want whatever is best for the kids,
“我要把最好的|西留o孩子
whether that means staying with us or returning to their birth mother. "
不管是和我在一起是回到H生母H身”
What if the judge reads that crap in front of Lizzy?
如果法官在利面前x到@句怎么k
That's why we wrote it like that, Mom.
@正是我下@句的原因
If she thinks our statement's the reason her mom doesn't get custody,
如果因殛述~е滤]有得到Oo
she's gonna hate us more than she does now.
她比F在更恨我的
She doesn't hate you. She just thinks you don't love her.
她不恨你  她只X得你不鬯
And that statement ain't gonna help.
@份述~⒁o所用
Did Lizzy tell you that? Oh, come on, Ellie.
是和您f的  哦  并不是  Ellie
I grew up a lot like that kid.
我的成Lv和那孩子很像
You get reminded what a sack of shit you are five times a day,
如果你每天都被人R你是屎
after a while, you can't believe anyone could ever love you.
^了一  你直不敢相信有人勰
You know that we love you, right?
你知道的我勰  Π
No.
是的 我知道
But that's not you, it's me.
但不是你 我畚易约
I thought I just covered all that.
我以槲乙呀可以看淡所有
But I do love you both.
但我真的勰
Get some sleep, kids.
孩子  睡一X把
After you fix that god-awful statement.
在那之前e忘了改改述~
Wow.
真的
It's so clean and quiet in here.
@里既整又安o
I know.
我知道
I hate it.
但我@
Me too.
我也是
Hey. Hey.
-嘿  -嘿
Guys. We are so sorry.
孩子  我很抱歉
We are so sorry. Are you okay?
我很抱歉  你]事吧
Guess what? We got a ride in a police car.
你知道  我坐著警^淼
You did? Was that fun?
是  有趣
Did you guys go to prison? No. We were... just in jail.
你MOz了  是  我…就在Oz里
Juan. Lita. Come on.
阮  塔  ^戆
Mom's here. Okay.
在@里  好的
Okay, folks, our .26 hearing is now a Change of Circumstance hearing
好的  各位  26C是P于S拉
for a Miss Carla Viara.
小姐的情葑更
And you are Miss Viara, yes? She is, Your Honor.
-你是伊莎白 S拉小姐  是的  法官大人
And also with us today are Juan, Lita, and Elizabeth Viara?
今天和我在一起的有阮  塔和伊莎白
Here. Here!
在@里  在@里
And did you two each get a teddy bear?
你都拿到泰迪熊了
Yes! Oh, those are good ones.
是的  哦  它很漂亮
And you are Elizabeth? It's Lizzy, sir.
-你是伊莎白  我是 先生
I mean, Your Honor.
我是f  法官大人
And, Lizzy, I understand that you've submitted a statement.
好的    我知道你已提交了一份明
And the foster parents, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner, are they present as well?
寄B家庭父母f戈夫D也在
Yes, Your Honor.
是的  法官大人
And, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner,
f戈夫D
is it accurate that you left Juan and Lita alone in your car
你因乐匾u舳被捕r  你把阮和塔
while you were being arrested for aggravated assault?
为留在了里
Well, that... Yes, Your Honor, but in our defense...
-嗯  那…是的  法官大人  但我是榱...
Sir, all I need to know is whether or not Lizzy is lying.
先生  我只P心Lizzy是不是撒e
No, she's not lying.
她然]撒e
And prior to that assault,
在那次打糁前
did you accost a 14-year-old honor student in the same school yard
你在校@里和一14q的三好W生搭
and encourage him "to whip out his big, shaved plums"?
并鼓钏掏出他光滑的蛋蛋
I said that, Your Honor, but again,
法官先生  我已f^了  并且
I thought it was the person who sent her the...
我X得是有人故意o她
Mrs. Wagner, did you at one time force Lizzy's friends to leave your
Wagner夫人  你曾一度迫Lizzy的所有朋友
home
x_你家
by way of a bedroom window?
呐P室窗里爬出去x_
It was a ground floor window. Good. Points for you.
那是一扇落地窗  那表P你了
And at that same occasion, did you tell Lizzy to call CPS and to come
同r你告VLizzy打叫CPS
and take the kids?
把他都接走
She didn't mean that. I did not mean that.
你`她了  我]想那么做
That was in the heat of an argument.
那次是在忸^上
Your Honor, I have a statement. Yes, I've read it, thank you.
法官先生  我有份情  我知道  看^了
We actually wrote a new one. Ma'am, excuse me, but I have your...
我重了一份  女士  那  不用了吧
Please, Your Honor, we were up late working on it. I can read it very
拜托  法官大人  我]日]夜的心血在@
fast.
我x的很快不耽`rg
"Lizzy once asked us why we took them in.
Lizzy曾我槭裁词震B他
And at the time, we couldn't answer her."
我ro言以
Ma'am, please sit down. Please, Your Honor, can you let me say
女士  你是坐吧  法官先生 允S我
the answer?
您能允S我f出答案
No. Sit.
不用了  坐吧
This hearing is not about you.
@雎Cc你oP
Judging by Lizzy's statement, you might be back in court soon enough,
Lizzy的明砜  我在@地方面
so let's save that heartwarming speech for that occasion.
所以f@些留o日后f吧
Okay. Now, Miss Viara,
Viara小姐
I see that you've been keeping up with your visits. That's good.
看砟阋恢痹诟M你的拜L  那很好
I also understand that you've been sober for the last five months.
我也明白你^去五月一直很清醒
Is that still the case?
F在是如此
Yes. That's very good news.
是的  那可真是好消息了
And if I were to put the kids in your care,
如果我你碚疹孩子
your current residence could accommodate them?
您家里住的下
I think so.
那]}
It's small, but it works... Your Honor.
麻雀m小  五K俱全的 法官先生
And, Miss Viara, do you feel capable of responsibly caring
Viara小姐  你X得你能肩起P心e人的重任
for Juan, Lita, and Lizzy at this time?
同r照Juan  Lita  Lizzy他三
Miss Viara.
Viara小姐
Mama.
女士你在
Yes, Your Honor. I'm capable now.
然  法官先生  ]}
Everybody get ready for dinner.
所有人涑酝聿屠
Here you go.
o你
What if when we go live with our mom,
如果以后和我一起住
she doesn't know how to make my noodles the way I like to have them?
她不知道怎么弄我鄢缘拿l花
Don't worry, pal. Lizzy will show her the way we do the cheese for you
伙e心  Lizzyo你做我做^的芝士
so your mom can make it for you just the way you like.
@幽不就做了
Yeah. Okay.
ε  e心啦
Come on, guys. Don't be sad on our last night.
我一起的最后一晚啦  大家e垂^獾
You know what? I think we should tell Pete and Ellie thank you,
我X得我感xPete和Ellie
you know, for everything they've done for us, yeah?
他真的槲付出很多 不是
Thank you. Well, thank you, pal.
xx你  我也要感x你 小家伙
Yeah, thank you, guys.
xx大家
Lita? I don't want to say anything.
Lita你呢  我不想f
Oh, honey.
怎么了
I'm just gonna go check on Lita.
我去瞅一眼Lita
I mean, unless you want to.
我意思是  除非你想
Yeah, I would, actually. Thanks.
其我想fxx
Come on, buddy. You haven't touched your pasta.
怎么了小家伙 你一勺都]
You want me to reheat it for you?
要不我o你在岚
It's okay, buddy.
]P系啦小家伙
That's okay, buddy.
不要y^  小家伙
Good night, buddy. Good night.
好  小家伙  晚安啦
Sweetie, good night. I love you.
晚安  我勰
Love you too.
我也勰
Okay, all your court bears are in here, the new ones as well.
你所有的球鲂芏荚谶@里啦  包括那些新的
Speaking of court, um,
f到@毫
I just wanted to apologize for what I wrote to the judge.
很抱歉  我o法官的那些
It was all true.
事如此
It was a little out of context maybe, but there's no hard feelings.
可能有c}  但是e往心里去
Actually, I wanted to give you the statement we wrote
其我也好想o你我的那份明
that we couldn't read in court, just so you have it.
就是法庭上]Cx的那封 你看吧
Guys, Mom's here.
小家伙  砝
All right. Get up! Come on. Let's go.
收拾|西 涑霭l
Lita, come on, get your stuff.
Lita  快去收拾你的|西
Bye, Meatball.
再咯  肉球
Hey. I've got a car seat for Lita if you don't have one.
嗨  我oLita多Я座  怕你@]
You guys picking us up? Where's Mom?
怎么是你斫游  呢
She was supposed to meet us at the office this morning
她今早和我在k公室碰面的
and she didn't show.
但她放子了
Oh, no.
我的天
She didn't answer her phone.
她也不接
Did you go to her house? What if something happened to her?
你去她家看了  f一她出事了呢
Yes, we went to see her. She was very ashamed.
我然去看了  她很羞愧
She said... she can't do it.
她f  她是做不到
No, she didn't. Because why would she, um, fill out all the forms
我不相信  如果她不想  槭裁匆填那么多表
and the court stuff and reunification stuff if she didn't...
M那么多事找法庭人TびH人T
Lizzy, your mom said you filled out all those forms. I helped,
Lizzy  你f你填完了所有表  我兔α
but so what?
有呢
She felt she was being pushed into something that she wasn't ready
她感X她在被逼著接受
for.
她]浜玫氖
No. I didn't push her. She's ready!
并不是  ]有人逼她  她已浜昧
Just let me talk to her, please,
我裾f吧
and then we can figure something out.
效果或S好一c
Honey. And she can take me home.
她本砟我回家的
Honey, when we saw her, it was obvious.
H鄣  我看到她第一眼就明白了
She's using again.
她又重蹈覆H了
She's not coming, baby.
她不砹
Sweetie, we're so sorry.
很抱歉
I'll go get her. You watch the kids.
我去找她  你留下看好孩子
Just wait there, okay? Lizzy!
在@里等我 好不好  Lizzy
Lizzy. Please just go away. You're not my parents.
Lizzy  不要管我了  你又不是我H生父母
No, we're not. But you know what we are? We're here.
是  你f得  但我永h陪伴你
That's right, we're here and we love you.
我一直在你身  用心去勰
What? No, you don't. You don't even know me.
怎么可能  你真的懂我
Hey, what the hell's going on out here?
@怎么了
Could you just give us a few minutes, please?
您能我为呆
Oh, okay. Sorry.
]}  不好意思啊
Lizzy, honey, we do know you.
Lizzy  H鄣  我然懂你
We... We know that you hate cheese,
比如你芝士
but you really love cheeseburgers.
但你又超喜g芝士h堡
And we know that when you feel good in the morning,
我知道  早上你要是心情好了
you put on a little less makeup than you do on the bad days.
你化的y比心情不好r淡一cc
Exactly. And we know that the most important thing in the world to you
]e吧  而且我知道  δ碚f
is to protect Juan and Lita from the things nobody protected you from.
世上最重要的事是保o好Juan和Lita
We know that about you, right? Yes, honey.
我f的  是不是
You guys are doing good.
你做的很棒了
I'm sorry. We know there's so much we don't know.
-Σ黄  -我知道有很多我不了解的事
But if you're afraid we can't handle knowing the bad stuff, or the
但如果你害怕我南息
scary stuff,
或可怕的事物理不好
we can, I promise.
我做得很好  我保C
Yeah, bring it. Whatever you got, we want it.
е@承Z  不管l生什么 一起面
Because we love you, Lizzy.
因槲勰  Lizzy
Stop saying that. Please just go away, please.
求你ef了  走吧
Please.
走吧
Is Lizzy okay? She's a little upset right now, buddy.
Lizzy好  小家伙  她F在有c
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm good.
那你好  我]事
Here she is.
看看l砹
So...
所以…
um, here's what I think is best.
我是X得@鹤詈
I know Juan and Lita are more like what you had in mind when you got
你陷入@件事的r候
into this.
你的X子里只有Juan和Lita
Come on, baby.
^
So I think the best thing is for you to adopt them.
我X得最好是你收B他
And... And I'll just ask Karen for, um, a different placement.
有  我Kareno我重新找地方
So... No.
所以  e@
No, it'll be good. No, honey.
]事  @幼詈  不  一c都不好
We need your help with Juan and Lita.
我需要你Juan和Lita呢
We're not doing this without you.
]有你我可做不到
I'll visit all the time and you can call me if you need help for
需要兔α穗Sr系我 我常
anything.
在家看看
No. Pete, I really don't want to argue about this right now.
不可能  Pete  我F在真不想檫@吵
I don't care. I said no. That's not happening, okay?
我不管  我f^那不可能  明白
You're with us now. Yeah.
你和我在一起
And you know why? We've got a cosmic connection.
你明白  我X得冥冥之中自有天意
That's right, we've got a cosmic connection.
我X得冥冥之中自有天意
I know you feel sorry for me right now, but you really don't have to..
我知道你F在可z我  你不用@
It's got nothing to do with what just happened.
和l生的一切都oP
Where's the court statement Ellie gave you?
Ellieo你的法庭述呢
See this? Read that.
看到]  大x
"Lizzy once asked me why we did this, why we took them in.
Lizzy曾我槭裁次收B他
We couldn't give her an answer at the time.
那r我o不了她答案
We did it because something was missing in our lives, but we didn't
@么做是因槲感X生命中e^了什么
know what it was.
我又然不知
It was Juan, Lita, and Lizzy."
原砭褪悄
You see?
明白了
You were what was missing, Lizzy.
你就是我缺少的那一K
But now you're here and you are stuck with us.
F在既然我在一起了
That's right. We're gonna be at every soccer game.
Π  我要出F在每球鲇蛑
We're gonna be all over your ass about your grades.
我δ愕某煽火冒三丈
We're gonna buy you your first prom dress.
我要o你I人生第一件舞Y服
It's gonna be really pretty. But not too revealing. Super sweet.
一定超好看的  既可塾植暴露太多
You know, not too sexy.
就那N不很性感的
Just like... really, that gorgeous sweet spot.
就像  你是最甜美的那
Yeah. And when you graduate high school,
ε  你高中I了
we're gonna be in the front row embarrassing you.
我在前排v你的糗事
We're gonna be in the front row again when you graduate college, or
你大WI的r候  我那么干
even if you don't.
或者不上都成
You will be graduating college, 'cause it's so important and you're
你一定大WI  你那么明
so smart.
δ碚f很重要
I don't mean to push, but it just opens up so many more opportunities.
我不逼你  但是大WIC遇更多
But either way, we're gonna be there for you.
但不如何  我都伴你左右
And someday I'm gonna give you away at your wedding.
直到某天  我在你的婚Y上送e你
Even if I think the guy's a pissant and he's not good enough for my
即使我J樗是笨蛋  他也不配
little girl.
我家小姑娘
That's right. Someday in the future.
多好啊  砟程
Someday in the way, way, way off, deep, deep, deep distant future.
bh而|不可及的未
Lizzy, can we go home now?
lizzy  我回家吧
Yeah, I guess we can.
我也@酉氲
I know you don't like this,
我知道你不喜g@
but you're gonna have to get used to it once in a while, okay?
但你偶也要T一下  好不好
Can I get one? I haven't gotten a single hug from you since I've
我能硪嘛  自奈艺JR你
known you.
我一都]抱^
Please?
o面子吧
Hi. I don't know the whole context of everything.
嗨  我m然不明白l生什么了
But I'm just wondering if I can just get in on that hug a little bit.
但我只想知道我能不能也抱一下下
We're good! Thank you so much. We're good, thank you.
不用不用  心I了  xx您
Sorry. That was just wrong. Yeah, I just do that. You guys hug.
Σ黄  我不@拥  你^m
I crossed a boundary there.
我有c^了
Everything's gonna work out great too.
一切也都好起淼
I can tell.
我敢保C
Hi!
嗨
Oh! Oh, thank you!
喔  太感x了
Bye. Bye!
再咯  回
Are you with them? Do you know those guys?
你一起  你JR他
Yeah. Why?
JR啊  怎么了
Do you guys want to come in?
你想M碜坐
Uh... I-I made a pie.
我  我做了岷醯呐
No, thank you. Yes!
不用了  xx  必去了
Karen! It's pie. You know I love pie.
Karen  那可是派啊  你不了解我
Great. Yeah, I just... I have so many feelings.
太好了 真的 我想法太多了F在
Go potty, put your shoes on. We're gonna go, okay?
上所  穿上鞋  我出l了  好
Okay!
好}
Whoa, Juan. What are you doing, buddy?
Juan  哥  你干嘛呢
You can't wear sneakers. We gotta look good today.
可不能穿\有  今天我得看起砜
Mom, have you seen my phone?
老你我手C了
Uh, no. Wait, you mean the one in your hand?
]啊 你意思是你手上那是吧
Lita, honey, did you go potty?
Lita  小  你上^所了
I went potty! Okay, good job.
我去^啦  非常棒
Everybody go potty! Yeah, I went potty.
全部上所去  我去^啦
Got that packet we're supposed to bring? Yeah, I'm all set.
上我要У陌裹了  -是的  都浜昧
Let's go, guys. Let's go.
出l咯  出l
I'm gonna beat you!
我要A咯
No, no, no.
然不行
No distracted driving, okay?
Ｐ拈_  行吧
All right. All right?
]}  _定
She's gonna drive. Oh, yeah?
她黹_  真的呀
Yes, but I have the phone and I'll sit in the front
是的  我拿著手C坐前排
in case I have to grab the wheel or shut down the power, okay?
以防我不得不抓方向P或者停  好
Sandy, come on, it's started!
Sandy  快c快c  要_始啦
Did I make it? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我]t到吧  好
What's that?
那是啥啊
Lizzy made it for me. You didn't get one?
Lizzyo我做的  你]有
You got a T-shirt? You got a T-shirt?
你居然得到了一短袖
You may all be seated.
T位就座
Good morning, folks.
大家早上好
You know, family court is important...
所周知  家庭法庭很重要…
Wait. Wait! Wait! Wait.
稍等一下  等等  等等
Grandma Sandy's in the house. We can begin.
Sandy奶奶就座完  可以_始啦
Told you we'd make it. Stop it!
我f的]e吧  e[
These seats are saved. Yeah, they're saved for me.
-@些座被占了  Π  就是o我占的
Move over. Stop it!
往^挪  e[啦
Go ahead, Judge. Thank you, Grandma Sandy.
法官先生您^m  感x配合  洛尼特奶奶
She got a T-shirt.
居然送她短袖
You know, family court is important work.
所周知 家庭法庭意x重大
But it's difficult work.
但是做好也不容易
We spend day in and day out dealing with things
我日鸵蝗盏靥理一些事情
that we feel no family should have to go through.
理我X得大家不面Φ氖虑
So on these rare days when we get to smile at work,
所以在@y得的滋炖  我笑起r
these days mean a great deal to all of us.
意味著@些任AM完成
And I may not look it, but I'm a huge cornball
我或S看不到  但我很多愁善感
and I live for this.
我以此而活
Yeah!
我懂
I love this song.
我超圻@歌
We are here today to officially create a new family.
今天大家共聚一起斫M建新家庭
Peter and Elinore Wagner,
Elinore  Wagner和Peter
do you wish to adopt Juan, Lita, and Lizzy into your family today?
今天你Q定好要和Juan Lita Lizzy成橐患胰肆
Yes, Your Honor. Yes, Your Honor.
毫o疑 法官先生
It's just the song that's got me a little emotional.
@歌的我多愁善感的
Juan, Lita, and Lizzy,
Juan  Lita  和Lizzy
would you like Peter and Elinore to be your mom and dad?
你愿意做Elinore  Wagner和Peter的孩子
Sure.
我愿意
Yes, please. Yes!
毫o疑  那必的呀
Well, then,
b于此
by the authority vested in me by the state of California,
按照法以及加州x予我的嗔
I pronounce you a family.
我宣布你正式成橐患胰
Here you go. Thank you.
o您  太感x了
Would you like to take a picture with the judge? Yeah, sure.
要和法官合影  那然了
Thank you.
xx
Yeah, let's do it.
戆
That's gonna be us soon.
R上我啦
Oh, I'm part of this family too.
有我呢  我也是@家的啊
Okay, thank you. Wait, me too!
哈哈 感x您  有我呢
I'd like to be in the picture. Are you sure? We're not...
我也想^去拍 你_定  我]
We should all go. I think they'd like that.
我一起去  他一定也愿意
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
那就走
Okay! Okay.
各就位啦
Anybody else?
都到R了
Yeah, you too. Come on!
有你呢  快一起
Okay, I think that's everybody.
@下AM啦
Say "Family." Family!
喊 全家福  全家福
HDZIMU http://www.hdzimu.com
HDZIMU中文字幕W http://www.hdzimu.com